<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>11050</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-01 17:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-01 09:31:07</logtime>
<subject>Second Class</subject>
<event>Today was my Mum&apos;s University Graduation. 2:1 in Psychology. Pretty good! 4 years of hard work and stress - thank god its over!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/congraduation.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Congradulations&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/spinning.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/mainhall.jpg&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>11430</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-02 18:03:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-02 10:17:26</logtime>
<subject>What a boring day</subject>
<event>So i got up at 11am, got a shower and breakfast and sat my rear end firmly on this very chair infront of my lovely computer. 

Its now 6pm...

I havent been on computer all day though. I watched a few episodes of Red Dwarf and watched All Grown Up (Rugrats), rolled a joint and stuck a pen up my nose. Mum and bro are out shopping. I think they are going to bring back dinner. Hopefully they will. Then I will consider going out once I&apos;ve eaten. Until that time comes I will be content sitting here for a bit longer. Unless i get really really bored. 

So today dad got new car. Nice 4 X 4. Should be fun. Only had a quick glance at it.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/4x4.jpg&quot;/&gt;

Im so bored. Got a lot that i can keep myself occupied with, mostly on computer; learning, doing something in general. But what i really want is to be with people... hmmm... Maybe something will crop up sometime. Im not workin today, but im workin tomorrow and hopefully I&apos;ll be able to work on Sunday and everyday next week would be nice. I want fucking money! 
&lt;P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music>Fear Factory</current_music>
<current_mood>bored</current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>11533</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-02 18:36:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-02 10:37:55</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;&lt;table width=250 align=center border=1 bordercolor=black cellspacing=0&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=black align=center&gt;&lt;font style=&apos;color:white; font-size: 16pt;&apos;&gt;obsolete_mind&apos;s LJ stalker is hynde!&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td align=center bgcolor=white&gt;&lt;font style=&apos;color:black; font-size: 12pt;&apos;&gt;hynde is stalking you because your LiveJournal is just SO damned interesting. They are also not very liked around here!&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;div align=center&gt;
&lt;BR&gt;&lt;form method=&quot;POST&quot; action=&quot;http://www.go-quiz.com/stalker/stalker.php&quot;&gt;LiveJournal Username:&lt;input name=&quot;uname&quot;&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;input type=submit value=&quot;Who is your LJ Stalker Friend?&quot;&gt;&lt;BR&gt;
&lt;/form&gt;
&lt;P&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>11832</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-02 18:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-02 10:55:25</logtime>
<subject>Ach you shouldn&apos;t have</subject>
<event>So my granny&apos;s moving back into her house soon. Me and chris were helping her move stuff in the house and she gave us a fiver! I will treasure it, its all the money I have - but its my bday soon! 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/fiver.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Fiver&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>12059</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-04 19:55:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-04 12:08:20</logtime>
<subject>I played golf!</subject>
<event>So me, dad and bro went to the gold club and played golf on the practice area. It was actually surprisingly fun!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/golf1.jpg&quot; /&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/golf2.jpg&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>12359</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-04 20:09:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-04 12:13:47</logtime>
<subject>The summer is here</subject>
<event>We&apos;re officially 4 days into the summer and i still feel a little crappy inside. I mean, the weather is great and i feel great cos i got no school etc. But i still have nothing to do. I&apos;m not going to be able to get any overtime in work for the next 2 weeks at least. This will probably mean i will be stuck in doors a lot of the time. 

If anyone wants to hang out with me give me a bell, i will be only too happy!! Anytime at all - i got no other plans.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>12559</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-05 20:21:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-05 12:25:33</logtime>
<subject>Just realised...</subject>
<event>My birthday is on a Thursday, next Thursay, and i work on Thursdays. Therefore I&apos;m going to be working on my Birthday. Ach well - its kind of Okay because I havent been able to get any overtime over the next couple of weeks I probably wont be working the rest of the week, other than Saturday as usual.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>13782</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-13 14:11:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-13 06:14:49</logtime>
<subject>No money, my computer and more virtual friends</subject>
<event>So over the last 2 weeks i have been on my computer solidly just about all day, of everyday, and I&apos;ve Enjoyed a lot of my days. Although i wish i could do more and could have done more in the first 2-3 weeks since finishing school, i know that it hasnt been feesably possible - my funds havent allowed for any costly activities. 

Unfortunately i have no been able to get any over time in work, which has really pissed me off. It was my big plan for the summer; to work everyday, about 30-40 hrs a week, and get £600-£700 a month. But that hasnt been happening at all. I have only been doing my contracted 10 hrs a week. Its fucking stupid really, they actually hired a few more people in my department (and i think a few other departments too). WHY!? Everyone, most people, want overtime in the summer! &lt;B&gt;I want overtime in the summer!&lt;/B&gt;, and im sure one of the main reasons i havent been getting it is because of the damn new-starts taking the extra hrs. 

Its been suggested to me to get a new job, and i&apos;ve thought about it, but i have been told that i should be able to get over time in about 2 or 3 weeks, this was about 2 weeks ago. I am hoping i &lt;I&gt;will&lt;/I&gt; be able to get overtime soon, and up to the end of the summer. I will also be hoping to transfer to another branch near the university if i get in, so i cant leave yet anyway. If i dont get to uni this year i will probably get a better job somewhere and work for a year etc. 

So working was my primary aim of the summer. My other was to spend a lot of time out of the house and off my computer... that has &lt;i&gt;not&lt;/I&gt; been going well at all. As I&apos;ve already said, i have spend everyday lately on my computer. I do like it, but i would be so much happier if i could have it differently. I want people... but then i realise that i dont have people. The people i care about... dont feel the same way. So i am left here while they are galavanting around, me probably not on their minds at all. Some would say its easy... but i cant just go uninvited. I do have some people i could visit, but they&apos;re really boring and sit around the house all day reading etc. I have absolutely no money which naturally limts all that i can do. So until now i will stay put i guess. 

I realise that i miss ronan more than i thought i would. One of the main reasons is because is one of the only real friends i have and vice versa. We are most always going to be doing fuck all until plans are made between us both. He gets back from France sometime next week. He will have no money, naturally, but i should hopefully have a little, birthday money and my pay, so that should get us somewhere i guess. It&apos;ll get me off my computer and out of the house a bit more anyway.

And Rachel, I am here, doing fuck all, gimme a call sometime...


So this afternoon, i was awoken by my manager. He let me know that i was supposed to be working from 9am to 5pm this today. This i am certain i was not made aware of, any extra hours i would most definately made a note of! Still half asleep i told him that i would come in a 3pm and work until 9pm. I am pretty pleased about this. Its what i have wanted. I just wished it could happen a little more. 

I am strangly really happy at the minute, i just feel i could be a lot happier. I guess the main reason that i am so happy at the minute is because i have finished school. I dont know if everyone else feels as pleased as i do, but i just cant get over it. Im in limbo. I am unsure whether i will get the grades required to get into my chosen university course. If it does happen i will be extremely pleased. If it doesnt, i know i will be a little disappointed, but its something that i am preparing for as i am not in anyway expecting straight As. If that does happen i will find a job and work for a year, getting into uni next year, or to a course which requires less grades and can enable me to skip the first year of the degree course (forget correct name of this course). 

So at the minute im just fuckin around. Sleeping until 1pm, not going to sleep until 3-4am, spending all day on computer and having no commitments. Its a great lifestyle, for a while. Theres no way i could do this all the time, but im liking it at the minute. 

Hopefully things will get better...</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>13898</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-13 21:25:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-13 13:33:10</logtime>
<subject>What a retard</subject>
<event>So i got into work and discovered not only was i supposed to be working today 9-6, but i was down to work on sunday too. I had not been made aware of any of this. Because i have a fixed contract of every Thurs and Sat i wouldnt normally check the schedule as i should be told, or asked, before being put down for extra hours. I hate retarded managers. I wouldnt have minded working on Sunday. 

Im working an extra 14 hrs on top of my usual 10 this week so its a bit of overtime anyway.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>14327</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-13 21:36:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-13 13:44:32</logtime>
<subject>Thanks Donny</subject>
<event>Yeah, i guess i should take the time to thank&lt;A HREF=&quot;www.donny.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Donny Osmond&lt;/A&gt;. It is because of him that my mum is away for today and again on Friday to see him in concert! It means that I wont be yelled every 2 minutes for me to get off the computer, help her with something stupid on the computer or hear about the fact that Donny just took a shit! 

A night without Mum, YAY!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>14401</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-14 03:52:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-15 07:18:30</logtime>
<subject>There&apos;s so much beauty in the world</subject>
<event>Mum came back today, saw her briefly before heading out to see &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0298148/combined&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Shrek 2&lt;/A&gt; with my brother, more on that later. She, however, is still her usual self. 

Its after half three and i feel really good. Ive just watched my new favourite film; American Beauty. It is a lot of what i love about life and how i feel about life. That there is so much beauty. I dont give a fuck about the conventionally &apos;hot&apos; chick with blonde hair, big tits and long legs. I would rather be with someone who is honest, about life and about themselves. That girl in the film is so beautiful. 

I am definately going to start going to a gym. Be more productive... 

There is so much about my current living state that i wish i could change. And if i could tomorrow i would. Unfortuately i need money to do most of these things. But because i am in a time of my life between posts, nothing set to stone as to what i am definately going to do after the summer, i can do a lot of things. I could leave the shit supermarket part-time job and get a fairly decent, for my age, full-time job, earn plenty of money, for my age, and enjoy myself, or go to university and have little money, but be out of the house and have a nice loan to look after me. 

They both have their pro&apos;s and con&apos;s. If i do get to university i will go for it. If i dont, i will also be pretty happy. Although i probably wont be able to move out, i will have a job and enough money to keep me happy. I will be able to get the material things that will make me happy for a while. Some new clothes, few upgrades to the computer, that sort of thing. But thats all that i really want. Other than that i just want to be happy and comfortable. As long as i have people around me that i love i dont need material things. 

&quot;I want to look good naked&quot;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>14816</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-15 15:19:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-15 07:54:31</logtime>
<subject>It&apos;s My Party and I&apos;ll Cry If I Want To...</subject>
<event>Its my Birthday. Im 19. 

I only got up at 14:45. Got shower, had breakfast, and here i am, at my computer again. As of yet my parents haven&apos;t given me anything for Bday. Just another day...
Working in 2hrs.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>14945</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-16 19:02:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-16 17:06:31</logtime>
<subject>Shrek 2</subject>
<event>I felt a little lost having not seen all of the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.imdb.com/title/tt0126029/combined&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;original movie&lt;/A&gt;. I remember watching it shortly after it was out on dvd, but getting a little bored half way through - not even half way through in fact. I just wasnt in the mood. Ever since then i wish i had seen it. I guess i just havent had the chance. But ever since i saw the trailers for the sequal I&apos;ve been in fits of laughter and eagerly awaiting its release. 

The &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.imdb.com/title/tt0298148/combined&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/A&gt; was a bundle of laughs the whole way through. I loved it. The soundtrack was spectacular. It was full of surprises and kept me hanging on for the entire duration. i have heard a few people say that its not better than the original... i have seen some clips since my first brief encouter and i regret not finding it as funny then as i do now. I feel there is something missing having not seen it. My goal is to ultimately see the original and then i think i will feel a lot better. Definately one (or two) to add to any great movie collection!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>15129</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-17 01:06:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-16 17:25:16</logtime>
<subject>Spidey-Sense...</subject>
<event>There has to be a sequal - though i have read that there &lt;I&gt;will&lt;/I&gt; be one so no need to think too hard about it. 

Tonight i saw &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.imdb.com/title/tt0316654/combined&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Spider-man 2&lt;/A&gt;. The eagerly awaited sequal. I will start by saying; it was worth the wait! Secondly, to get it out of the way, i will say; Kirsten Dunst is so &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Movies/kirstendunst07.jpg&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;very&lt;/A&gt; &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Movies/dunst.jpg&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;very&lt;/A&gt; &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Movies/Kirsten%2520Dunst.jpg&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hot&lt;/A&gt;!!

2 years after first being biten by the spider, Peter Parker is having trouble holding a job as a delivery boy, newspaper photographer and falling behind in his school work. Of course spiderman is to blame. Then there&apos;s Mary Jane. The love of his life, but is she his prioty? Does he have his prioties in order? A major identity crisis takes over. Then he meets Otto Octavius. He is a scientist who is trying to create a fusion energy source, and being funded by Harry Osborn&apos;s Company as a means of bringing more fortune to himself. Harry is also determined to discover the true identity of Spider-Man.

All of this comes together nicely in an amazing film filled with great action scenes and great special effects. There are a few things that anoyed me about the film. First there is Peter Parker&apos;s inability to talk. He stays silent too much. He is a nervous guy... but that nervous? Also the script. Some of those lines are unbelievable. But it is a comic book so can we really expect much more, and its also made with kids in mind as well as the adults. 

Overall i loved it!! I would see it again, if seeing movies more than once in the cinema was my thing, but its not.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>15481</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-25 17:16:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-25 09:20:13</logtime>
<subject>My Body-clock is fucked</subject>
<event>I only got up at 3:40pm today! The reason being because i didnt go to sleep until 5:30am!! In order for me to have the internet in my room i rely on the computer downstairs to be on. That computer currently isnt working, so mums laptop is in its place. Normally my parents turn the computer off when they go to bed because they cant sleep with the noise of it &apos;cos its right outside their bedroom. Well last night after watching &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0115641/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Beavis and Butthead Do America&lt;/A&gt; i turned on the laptop on my way to my room. I then sat on my computer until 5:30, when i started getting slightly tired. Thats really one of the things i wish i could do; to be able to carry on a conversation with people with so long, people that i dont really know that well. Maybe sometime

I got paid on Friday, and proceeded to spend about £90. HIM tickets, Drink, buses, Food, other random crap throughout the day. Most importantly is the HIM tickets. Definately going, looking forward to it!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/HIMtickets.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;HIM Tickets&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

I got very drunk on Friday night. It was fun. I hadnt been drunk in a few months! Then i woke up on saturday with a massive hangover and had to make my way home and it was very hard. Then i was a bit late for work too. Until the next time...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>15681</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-28 00:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-27 16:32:47</logtime>
<subject>Damn i want some Wotsits</subject>
<event>I decided to go buy some beer tonight. 4 cans of Bud. 4 cans of Harp. A Quarter bottle of Vodka. Bottle of coke and a packet of Wotsits. Now i got a massive craving for some more wotsits. Im gona watch American Beauty in a few mins, then i very well may take the 15min walk up to the 24hr shop and buy some wotsits.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>15978</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-28 00:58:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-27 17:10:47</logtime>
<subject>I need to Pee!!!</subject>
<event>Ive drank a few cans of beer and i do really need to pee right now. But the toilet is 2 floors down - cos the bathrooms being done up - OK going now!! ahhhhhh leaving it too long</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>16368</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-28 01:52:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-27 17:52:44</logtime>
<subject>Feels good</subject>
<event>Budweiser and Vodka great things; alcohol in general. Mixed with Damien Rice, BON JOVI THe streets -  other great music. Im gona inseert a few delinberate spellin mistakes so that it looks like im actually drunk. Of course i could just chekc it before hiting the &apos;send butting down here, but if i leave em in it does look a little more realistic i guess. Meah....

Go you - You and your little game. The bastards would know me down i just know it. I should sahve my legs and wear a short skirt and ... im goin a little too far right?

Yea i am. Ach who cares... NO dont say any more - everyone can read this! They dont care and you dont want them to!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>16584</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-28 04:49:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-27 21:04:32</logtime>
<subject>Finish</subject>
<event>I guess i should finish up. I didnt watch American Beauty. Instead i watched &apos;The Late Show with David Letterman, then some part of the highlights of the F1 race at the weekdn - which schmacher won again, then part of a basketball match. I really do like american sports - except American Football.

Go Me! 



And You!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>16674</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-29 03:00:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-28 19:00:57</logtime>
<subject>I like Budweiser better than Harp</subject>
<event>Its a fact - Bud is better than Harp. Harp is a close second thought. But this is only because better as a rule tastes like shit. But after 2 or 3 you dont notice so much so you keep drinking, then you get tipsy and you begin to really like the taste; then drunk. Although i would only usually drink 2 or 3 before moving onto the spirits; vodka and coke, southern comfort and coke and a few alcopops. I find that beer makes you feel very full before getting you drunk, so i dont usually get drunk just drinking beer because i get really full on them and have to stop before i&apos;m drunk - and that pisses me off.

I really like the &apos;Late Show with David Letterman.&apos; I have actually watched his show for the last 3 days in a row. Funny guy, but i dont really like how he interviews people; he would ask a question, let them talk abit but then interupt them while they are doing to ask another question which is usually just on another topic area. He doesnt really like to keep a topic going on for very long. He also reads from his cards a lot, which shows that he doesnt really know what to say a lot of the time and that he doesnt write most of it, which you can tell by the way he says it and the fact that he often says, &quot;It says here...&quot; I seem to have more bad things to say about him than good. Wonder how that worked out. Do I really actually like him?</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>17114</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-29 03:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-28 19:24:16</logtime>
<subject>Update Journal?</subject>
<event>I have the update page open for 15mins now... but i cant remember what i was gona say. This&apos;ll do.

I really am abusing this lately. Or maybe its a good thing.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>17169</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-07-31 03:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-07-30 19:41:38</logtime>
<subject>Golden Touch</subject>
<event>Played Pool, got slightly drunk and watched Donnie Darko. 

That was My Friday. Its 3:35am and im sitting at the flat listening to the compilation CD that i made last week and left here. Listening to Razorlight - Golden Touch. Its such a great song!! Right now im listening to it for the second time in a row. It is amazing. I dont know what it is about this song... but i truely love it. 

Unfortuantely i wont be able to go to Donegal this weekend. I feel i will be missing out on those times together. I want to go things together, you are one of my best friends and i want to spend a lot of time together but dont get the chance to enough. It just aint fair...

i gotta go to bed now cos im working tomorrow. Im going to give my newly written CV to a few shops tomorrow in the hope of getting another job cos ive had enough of only working 12 fucking hours a week - i want more money so that i can &lt;i&gt;can&lt;/i&gt; really enjoy myself. 

Enough said - time for sleep





&quot;I know a girl with a golden touch...&quot;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
