<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>17493</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-01 03:36:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-02 03:00:45</logtime>
<subject>Still alone...</subject>
<event>Today i awoke at 3pm, to the sound of my dad and brother leaving the house on a trip to portaferry (dont ask why). I probably would have gona had i got up slightly earlier. 

Instead i turned on the computer and there i stayed until 6:20. The time that mum arived home from work and dad and chris arrived back home (not sure whether they both got home together or a few mins apart, but i know there wasnt much of a time difference. 

So i caught up with whatever boring crap they got up to, ate my first meal of the day; a lovely lasagne, came back to computer, had a coffee at Clements, then bought some alcohol on my way home. I got home, come to computer, did usual crap, drank a bit, watched some tv, listened to some music; the usual - and here I am 3:29am. 12 hours after getting up. 

Today i downloaded the New Modest Mouse album and Interpol album from 2002 &apos;Turn On the Bright Lights,&apos; both are great!! 

If anything keeps me alive its music! 

And the prospect of having someone to love the the future. It may not be you, but i can dream can&apos;t I.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>17712</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-03 10:40:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-03 02:43:55</logtime>
<subject>Happy Birthday Hetfield!!</subject>
<event>YUP its &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/324321.jpg&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;James Hetfield&lt;/A&gt;&apos;s Birthday and im going to take these first few lines today to wish him all the best! 

But i guess a little more importantly is the fact that its my Mum&apos;s Birthday today also. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/mumbday1.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>18141</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-04 21:36:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-04 13:45:03</logtime>
<subject>Well.... that was shit</subject>
<event>Is it just me? Parties are supposed to be fun, right? I would put it mostly down to the fact that i didnt know most of the people and most of the time they were talking about some crap that i dont know anything about nor care about, such as soaps, comics and movies i havent seen.

I was smokin a lot of pot... i dont know if it has anything to do with it, i would really say it does, but sort of in a way i guess it does. Or maybe they just arent my sorta people. 

Whatever it was... i didnt really like sitting there all day on my own... smoking. 

Went to bed at about 3am, and managed to sleep quite well actually. Got up about 2pm. I &lt;I&gt;do&lt;/I&gt; love it when i have nothing to get up for and i really can just stay in bed until i am no longer tired. 

I got up and went on the PC for a while then came home. 

Its oh so boring. 

I did manage to do something in trying to get another job. I emailed a local company my CV yesterday, got an application from somewhere else and asked around a few other places. 

But until then i will be doing my usual crap ... &lt;B&gt;ABSOLUTELY FUCK ALL&lt;/b&gt;. FUN FUN.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>18735</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-04 22:16:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-04 14:17:30</logtime>
<subject>I got a Gmail account</subject>
<event>A very nice guy on &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.bluelight.nu&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bluelight&lt;/A&gt; gave me a &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://gmail.google.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Gmail&lt;/A&gt; account still having couple of invites left. I feel so special. I&apos;ve always wanted one, and now i have one. YAY!

Only problem is none of my friends even know what it is...

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/tech/GMAIL.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Gmail&quot; width=&quot;700&quot; height=&quot;400&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>19117</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-08 23:09:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-08 15:55:55</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Its madness! Ive got more contacts than i think i can handle now. I used to just have a  sensible number; a few people that i would talk to regularly, now theres lots, and we&apos;ve met now too!

So yesterday was Gay Day. They all paraded around and around until they eventually stopped and got drunk, as gays do i guess.

Then we went back to rosses, got stoned, went back to town, met a guy sniffin&apos; glue, got £40 between 3 of us to help take down marquee, went to the Front Page. There we saw 2 bands; both of whom gave me a sore head. Though i did realise that one of em was &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://listen.to/asylum666&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Asylum&lt;/A&gt; and im afraid it just isnt my thing. 

Then we went for a drink or two somewhere else and thats when i got really bored and tired. It was 1am, i had no cigarettes no drink and no money. Ronan was staying at mine and I didnt tell my parents i would be home so late. So we eventually left the shitty hall at 3am!! Walked to taxi depot and got taxi home. 

It was hell. All in all great day - but didnt end so great. 

Not to allow the bad to over shadow the good. I met some of the people ive been talking to online for over a month now and had great time!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>19380</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-09 04:54:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-08 20:54:50</logtime>
<subject>I killed a wasp!</subject>
<event>I used all my power and strength and managed to kill a wasp that got into my room and scared the shit outta me floating around my lamp beside me. My heart begins to pound when it flys out of sight. Armed with a large piece of cardboard and an pen i waited until it was crawling on the table, then i hit it with the edge of the cardboard and stabbed it a couple of times with the pen. When i was sure it was dead i put it onto the cardboard, threw it out the window and that was the end of that. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/wasp.jpg&quot;&gt;

Time for bed i should think...</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>19494</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-09 23:50:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-09 16:17:18</logtime>
<subject>Good Day</subject>
<event>Today was rather interesting. I met rachel in town at 3:30 and went for coffee then went and played pool. Finally someone i can beat! Only kiddin. Later we went back to rachels for dinner. That was scary. I was scared the whole bus journey. I mean - me at that house on any day other than a sunday - it just didnt seem right. Like i felt slightly wrong. But it went okay in the end, I even got a nice dinner there! 

Later we got a lift to the Odyssey where we met shit loads of people that ive never met before in my life. And then we started bowling. I played crap! I actually missed the pins completely twice! It was crap. As you can see below - i came last!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/bowling.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>19768</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-10 18:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-10 10:35:01</logtime>
<subject>Stoned again...</subject>
<event>When im stoned i end up really thinking about things in a lot of detail. I would be lying in bed with a million thoughts running through my head. I often want to write them down cos i know i wont remember it in the morning. So last night i got outta bed, searched for paper and pen and started writing down what i was thinking. It was one of those times where i got really depressed for a while. I lay there and wished that i had a mobile. I got a massive urge to send a txt message. To talk to someone... Its things like this that give me real determination to do what i want to do...

&lt;lj-cut text=&quot;Heres what happened&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Personal/journal.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/lj-cut&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>20066</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-11 15:05:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-11 07:06:16</logtime>
<subject>Like a baby</subject>
<event>I slept like a baby last night. I got a new pillow and its the most comfortable thing ever!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/Dscf0009.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>20354</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-12 16:41:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-12 08:41:54</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Oh thats great - you ask me out the very day that im working and i only work 2 days a week. 
Tomorrow it is!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>20565</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-12 23:58:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-12 16:00:40</logtime>
<subject>God Help Me!!!</subject>
<event>AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH This is not good!!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/Dscf0015s.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>20747</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-13 03:05:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-12 19:01:39</logtime>
<subject>I feel like writing.... just gotta think of something to write about</subject>
<event>So its 2:05am and im talking to canadian guy on msn about why he dislikes baseball and basketball. I watched a programme on Channel 4 about &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.allmusic.com/cg/amg.dll?p=amg&amp;token=&amp;sql=11:rzaxqj7yoj6a&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Muddy Waters&lt;/A&gt;... oh crap its now 3.00am now... 

I cant be bothered any more - maybe tomorrow...</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>21052</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-13 14:22:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-13 06:22:43</logtime>
<subject>Six Days</subject>
<event>I&apos;m becoming what i did not want to become. Im getting to like this journal thing too much, and its turning into the first and last site I visit every day.

Im beginning to write stupid crap for the s ake of it instead of semi-inteligent rants about life, politics, movies, music and technology. But do I want to do that either? I dont even know. All I know is im not happy. 

I want to actually &lt;I&gt;do&lt;/I&gt;stuff and then write about it, just just eternally write in hopppe that something better will happen and that eventually I will get off this computer and get a &lt;B&gt;Fucking Life!&lt;/B&gt;

I am just doing this to pass the time. I want more!

At first I thought the whole journal thing was stupid. In some ways I do still believe that. Im still not going to go into lots of detail about my life and the people around me, cos personally not everyone needs to know everything - and if i do say anything it sure wont be for the whole world to read. 

I do realise that it is a good idea. It gives me somwhere to write down my thoughts and for those i know to understand me slightly, if thats&apos;s possible. 

The way I want it to be is that I actually write about stuff that &lt;I&gt;happens&lt;/I&gt; occasionally. But nothing ever happens. 

The scary thing is - I have only 6 days left to wait...

In SIX days things will change. Ever since June I have simple been living to pass the time until Aug 19th. That is when i get my results. I will be doing one of two options. If my results go one way I will be going to &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ulster.ac.uk/campus/magee/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Magee University, Derry&lt;/A&gt; to try and start a new life and live in a world where I dont get mocked on my way to the local shop. If that doesnt happen I will have to stay right here; get a full time job and work on going to Uni next year. Of course this option wont be too bad - and in a way im also looking forward to it. 

The way I see it is that this is my life and i decide what happens and whether I enjoy it or not. Not getting to university is not the end of the world. There are plenty of other good options. And whatever does happen I am going to make sure it is good and that I enjoy it. 

If i do go for the 2nd option I will have plenty of money and i know that in the short term money &lt;I&gt;will&lt;/I&gt; make me happy for a while. I know money isnt everything, but i will be hapapy for a while with some. 

Then maybe i will be able to write something worth while here...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>21334</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-14 00:45:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-13 17:25:48</logtime>
<subject>WonDerland</subject>
<event>Up at 1:30, breakfast at 2:30. Town 5:00. Ronan still asleep! Went with Rach to play pool. Big American tables with crap cues. Fries at Burger King. Cigarettes. Ronan finally turns up at 7:30, fresh outta bed! 

We went to Auntie Annies for a bit then back to Burger King to smoke and converse until the movie started at 9:15.

The movie in question is &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.imdb.com/title/tt0335563/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Wonderland&lt;/A&gt;. In short - this was one awesome, fucked up, truthful mind-blowing, wonderful film. Its about John Holmes, a legendary porn star in the 60s and 70s. The story revolves around the murder of 4 people in a house on Wonderland Avenue on July 1, 1981. We hear the story from both David Lind, one of the &apos;lads&apos; and John himself. Both giving slightly different stories as to what happened in an attempt to discover who killed, or who should be convicted of committing this quadruple homicide. 

The film reveals the seedy world of drugs and violence in such great detail and was a thril to watch! 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/wonderland.jpg&quot;&gt;

Great film, great day outdoors!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>21648</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-14 13:29:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-14 05:30:26</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Damn Im such a sentimental guy i really am. Reading over some old MSN conversations. I laugh and i cry. I just wish i could talk to some people in person the way i do over fucking msn. Maybe i&apos;ll get better at it...</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>21832</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-15 20:16:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-15 12:29:08</logtime>
<subject>Anything better on?</subject>
<event>I mean seriously. You selfish fucking bastard! I dont want to watch fucking swimming all fucking afternoon and i dont think everyone else does either. Get a fucking life. Get off your fucking ass and be sociable! AAAHHHHHHHHHHHH *Expresses anger loudly*


On a Lighter note - i want an iPod. Those things ROCK! Was playin with Helens today and i loved it!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>22194</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-15 23:21:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-15 15:23:53</logtime>
<subject>Countdown</subject>
<event>so whats gona happen is  this - i work tomorrow - with no money or cigarettes to keep me going - and the same with tuesday - then i sit on my computer all day wednesday - then thurs i phone school and get results (cos theres no way im going back to that shit hole!) then work thursday evening - again with no cigarettes unless ive manage to scrape some money by then - t hen friday - i get paid - so i get cigarettes and very drunk!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>22435</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-16 12:28:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-16 04:29:33</logtime>
<subject>Holy Shit!</subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/Dscf0005.jpg&quot;&gt;
This motherfucker was in my room as i was goin to sleep last night!
It isnt as big as the picture luckily enough but it was pretty damn big</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>22607</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-17 22:02:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-17 14:14:05</logtime>
<subject>9am - 6pm</subject>
<event>Today i worked from 9-6. Dad left the house at about 8am, i got up at about 8am. I left at 8:30. I went out the back door. Dad had also gona out the back door. He hadnt opened the main front door. Mum and bro are in portstewart. I closed the back door, walked round to the front of the house and said &quot;SHIT!&quot; Yup i noticed the door hadnt been opened. I didnt have the key for it. I would have to get into the house via secret entrance. 

At lunch i came home from work cos i had no money and needed food. I squeezed through secret entrance. Luckily i managed. I ate. I left for work again, feeling much better with lots of food in me. 

While i was home i noticed a letter addressed to me. I opened it and it was from Dunnes Stores. 
&lt;lj-cut text=&quot;I got interview on Thursday for job there. This is good. &quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Personal/dunnes.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/lj-cut&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>23018</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-18 13:05:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-18 05:32:53</logtime>
<subject>Holy fuck its tomorrow!!</subject>
<event>AHH SHIT! I get my results tomorrow! This is not funny at all. Im scared. To add to the nervousness I also have a job interview tomorrow. So right now im gona go get some breakfast, get a shower and head into town to get some new shoes. :) 

HELP!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>23522</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-20 04:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-19 20:35:35</logtime>
<subject>ACCEPTED AND PLACED!!</subject>
<event>Lots of commotion with me today... actually it starts from last night. Mum and Chris had minor car accident in Coleraine. I was out at the flat at Agincourt trying to ring Dad to give me a lift home cos it was so wet. I kept ringing but there was no answer. At about 10 Ronan D told me that Ronan W told him that my parents were in Portstewart. Dad went up to see how they were, which is why i couldnt get in contact with him. So they all stayed in Portstewart and i got the house to myself. Unfortunately i couldnt take advantange because i had to get up
early this morning. 

So this morning i got up at 8:30. I phoned the school at about 10am and got my results. CCD. I needed CCD. Then i got changed and went into town for interview at Dunnes Stores. It went alright i think. Afterwards i walked around town for a while trying to get job application forms. Got a form for the Gadget Shop and Phones 4U. Anyway - when i got home i looked up Magee&apos;s website and tried to find out what to do about my results. After a while i noticed that it said &quot;including CC&quot; that made me think i had gotten in. I saw somewhere else &quot;Minimum of 240 points.&quot; Then i found website to translate my grades into points. I someone calculated that i got 240 points and then got all excited for 5 minutes. Then i did it again and realised that i only got 220 points. I was gona phone the university and find out what could be done. Then at the bottom of the page with the contact details it had a link to a site. So i went to the site and keyed in my application number. Then i was brought to a page that i now love. Well underneath the word &quot;Decision&quot; was the words &quot;Accepted and Placed.&quot; I now love those words!!

From that moment on i have been pretty much on a high. I am so happy that im going to be going to University. The moment i have been waiting for for a long time. Moving out of this house and moving out of Belfast!! I just couldnt be happier right now!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>23667</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-25 02:27:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-24 18:29:11</logtime>
<subject>Back</subject>
<event>Back from Portstewart where ive been since Sunday. Also not long back from the limelight - im pretty drunk, so much so that i cant write too much right now. Tomorrow...</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>24016</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-25 14:43:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-25 06:43:48</logtime>
<subject>Lets go fly a kite</subject>
<event>I went with my dad and brother to portstewart. Our main purpose was to go to a Kite festival/show/event on the Strand beach. We got there a little late but still had fun. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf0015.jpg&quot;&gt;

Then it started raining so we went back to the house and watched the boring olympics and some crappy football match.

Later ronan and i went to the golf club for a few pints with my dad then we played snooker. Great full size table, in a big room just to ourselves! Was a lot of fun.

We got home, watched more crappy olympics, watched Anger Management, then played Monopoly with Chris until 3am. 

On monday we went to Derry to get my accommodation in the University Halls sorted. We got a tour around the halls, which are very nice! Running around trying to find an ATM that works, then get passport photos, then find my UCAS number all to fill out the application form is not very funny at all. 

Yesterday i got a bus for Portstwewart to Coleraine, then got the train from Coleraine home. Was fun. Different.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>24153</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-25 17:49:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-25 10:17:02</logtime>
<subject>128mb</subject>
<event>Today my dad bought a new memory card for the digital camera. 128MB instead of 16MB!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf0004.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>24530</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-08-26 09:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-08-26 01:18:14</logtime>
<subject>Bonjour?</subject>
<event>Its 09:10am. We&apos;re leaving in about an hr to the airport. The plane leaves at about 12. Im all packed. Im lookin forward to it very much! 

The forecast is as follows:

Today - Showers - High 21 - Low 11
Tomorrow - Partly cloudy - High 23 - Low 15
Saturday - Light rain - High 21 - Low 9
Sunday - Partly Cloudy - High 21 - Low 9
Monday - Scattered Showers - High 20 - Low 11

Damn... it could be better. Aw well.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
