<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>599</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-09 21:13:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-09 13:23:42</logtime>
<subject>Here I Am</subject>
<event>Yea i thought you know, since everyone else has one, I want one too! Here it is, and here i am. I have given into the invasion of anonymity and &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://privacy.net/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;privacy&lt;/A&gt; that is Blogging!

I guess it aint that bad since the only people who can actually see this are my &apos;friends&apos;. Then it seems really pointless. Maybe i need more friends. Just so i can tell them all my private stuff? Nah ... ach well. Im here anyway, lets see how long this lasts. 

Im not sure how interesting this will ever be i dont really do much of great interest. And if its that interesting... it will probably be illegal or something that i wont actally want anyone to read. 

I dont have much to say now ... Im in a reasonable mood i guess. I should get on with some more work in a minute i think, tidy my room, and if i was really good i would do the hoovering as i was asked to do earlier... but im not so i&apos;ll do it tomorrow, maybe. 

Ach this is all i can really think of for now. Im listening to Everclear ... now &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.megadeth.com/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Megadeth&lt;/A&gt;. I dont want to listen to Megadeth right now... lets see. OK i&apos;m in the mood for &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.4ad.com/artists/catalogue/pixies/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Pixies&lt;/A&gt; - Monkey Gone to Heaven, good song! 

Here&apos;s a pic i took today of my bro walkin up the stairs. I love the way the light shines though the window!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/chris_stairs.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Chris&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>831</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-10 00:18:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-09 16:34:31</logtime>
<subject>Spoon or Knife</subject>
<event>I did it again! I was eating my usual bowl of Weetabix before goin to bed. I went to the cutlery drawer to get a spoon, but instead i picked out a knife! A KNIFE! How am i going to eat Weetabix with a knife. I dont know what it is, but i seem to do this quite a lot. Spoon for buttering bread, Fork for eating a yoghurt. It really frustrates me cos i feel really stupid. Of course no-one else sees me do it other than me, unless my mum or someone is in the kitchen at the time and i go so far as to take it out of the drawer, and even set it down on the table/sideboard or whatever. 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/cutlery.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Cutlery&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>1103</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-10 00:59:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-09 17:05:44</logtime>
<subject>Ace of Spades</subject>
<event>As has been happening every other day for the past few weeks, I played cards again with chris just a few mins ago. Did pretty weel, but we have both gotten so good that we know what each other is going to do, and especially when one of us has an ACE (which means the other person has to pick up 5 cards, or put down an ACE meaning they have to then pick up 10 cards and so on). It means that we always leave our ACES until the end... and then it gets pretty tough, not very fair i guess. So i stopped playing in the middle of a game, cos its really late and i got school in the morning, plus i really gotta tidy my room here, and get some stuff ready for school. At the min he has just had to pick up 15 cards and i only have 3 cards. We will continue tomorrow!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Playingcards.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Jack Change it&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>1400</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-10 20:24:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-10 12:47:03</logtime>
<subject>SUN!</subject>
<event>Today was a fuckin beautiful day! Shortly after i got home from school i went into town and took some snap-shots of things shitty city on one of the rare occasions that it gets lots of sun and heat. I took a walk around the Lagan Look-out, the Waterfront, then to Botanic Gardens. Heres what i saw:

This is of the big fish by the Lagan:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/bigfish.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Big Fish&quot; /&gt;

This is a pic of the Lagan from the Waterfront:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/lagan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;The Lagan&quot; /&gt;

Heres a pic of the Waterfront Hall
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/thewaterfront.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;The Waterfront Hall&quot; /&gt;

This one is of lots of people sitting at Botanic Gardens:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/botanic.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Botanic Gardens&quot; /&gt;

Finally, I managed to really make the Ormeau Bridge look good! (It was tricky)
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/ormeaubridge.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Ormeau Bridge&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>1604</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-10 23:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-10 16:03:57</logtime>
<subject>Damn Network!</subject>
<event>The main computer in the house hasnt been working great lately. So today i tried to setup the mum&apos;s new &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.computers.toshiba-europe.com/cgi-bin/ToshibaCSG/model_index_page.jsp?z=59&amp;service=UK&amp;ID=2326/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;laptop&lt;/A&gt; with net connection and get my internet though the laptop. I tried a million times, fidling with &lt;A HREF=&quot;www.symantec.com/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Norton Firewall&lt;/A&gt;, the Home Network Connection Setup etc, but to no avail! So about 10mins ago i gave up and stuck the network connections back into the main computer, which is working, but not very well.

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/laptop.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Laptop&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>1952</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-11 10:15:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-11 08:17:45</logtime>
<subject>What about blogging</subject>
<event>I’ve just spent the last 30mins or so reading some articles I printed yesterday on &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BBC News&lt;/A&gt; relating to &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.google.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/A&gt; and &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Blogging&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Blogging&lt;/A&gt;. It appears that Blogging is... well, huge. Yeah in case you didn’t already know that, its fuckin massive. Blogger had 200,000 users last year, yup a full year ago, before Google took over! Now I cant imagine how many millions of people use Blogger along. &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.livejournal.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Livejournal&lt;/A&gt; say they have 3,082,448 subscribers, of which 1,482,196 are described as active. And there are so many more blogging services and tools out there! 

Me on the other hand, I’m not trying to get publicity, fame or to be noticed. I just feel its time to put some stuff on the web. In my case a lot of pictures, because I love taking pictures of the world around me and the people with me. I realised this about a year ago really. That pictures must be taken of things that happen to us or else we will just forget these things happened. 

I’m not going to go mad on the self-indulgent, self-opinionated drivel that comes from a lot of blogs. I want mine to be a place where I can share the out of the ordinary, bizarre, slightly interesting, accounts of my days. Maybe the odd rant, the odd bit of opinion (well I’m not going to be writing much of other people’s opinions), the occasional boring stuff… but I will keep that to a minimum. 

So basically, I don’t care if you read this or not. I’m not writing this for the masses, nor am I doing it so I can get more ‘virtual friends’, I’m simply doing it as a way of recording my life, through pictures and words. If you are some random stranger living in a distant land, or round the corner, that’s fine by me… just don’t come looking for me cos you were slightly offended by anything I may say!
 
&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/3694691.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Google revamps blogging service (BBC News)&lt;/A&gt;

&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/3078541.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;A Blog For Everyone (BBC News)&lt;/A&gt;

&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/3134629.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;All over for blogs? (BBC News)&lt;/A&gt;

&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/sci/tech/2775249.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Fame or misfortune beckons for weblogs? (BBC News)&lt;/A&gt;

&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/in_depth/sci_tech/2000/dot_life/1799998.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;I blog, therefore I am (BBC News)&lt;/A&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>2232</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-11 16:20:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-11 09:38:46</logtime>
<subject>Burnt Toast!!</subject>
<event>Here&apos;s what happens when you leave toast in the grill in an attempt to make a cheese toastie, and then end up forgetting about it. I really have never seen toast like this before, nor have i seen the amount of smoke that resulted come from two slices of toast! Just don&apos;t ask my brother to make a cheese toastie!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/burnt_toast.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Burnt Toast&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>2496</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-11 21:00:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-11 13:33:03</logtime>
<subject>O2 giving away free SIM cards?</subject>
<event>I dont know why it happened, but im certainly not going to complain about it either. I got 2 free &lt;A HREF=&quot;www.o2.co.uk&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;O2&lt;/A&gt; SIM cards in the post today. When i bought my O2 SIM card in December i paid £13 for it if i remember correctly. Now i hear they cost only a fiver, or less. Its a bit of a bitch, but its the way the market works. 

I guess if they&apos;re that cheap no one will want to buy them off me. Unless i find some dumb people who dont know how much they cost at the min... or i could try and sell them on &lt;A HREF=&quot;www.ebay.co.uk&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Ebay&lt;/A&gt;. Having just checked Ebay it would appear there are &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://phones.listings.ebay.co.uk/Sim-Cards_O2_W0QQsacategoryZ29779QQsocmdZListingItemList&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;some for sale&lt;/A&gt; at the minute on Ebay, some 1272 of them!

&lt;A HREF=&quot;http://search-completed.ebay.co.uk/ws/search/SaleSearch?SaleSearch&amp;sacategory=29779&amp;so=Show+Items&amp;sapricehi=&amp;gotopage=&amp;soitemstatus=2&amp;lopg=&amp;sofocus=so&amp;sapricelo=&amp;sosortproperty=1&amp;sotr=2&amp;from=R2&amp;catref=C6&amp;sosortorder=1&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Recently ended auctions &lt;/A&gt; have gone something like this:
2 O2 Sim Cards 300 Txts + WAP - Consecutive No.s 94/95! - £12.95
O2 Sim Pack 300 Free Texts Month 300 Wap Mins PAYG - £4.99
o2 sim cards with 300 free texts free p&amp;p  - £6.95
o2 sim card 300 free txts&amp;wap+info - £7.00

But im not sure i wanna sell em, Might come in handy some time. Plus they got a cool(ish) number. 07*** 420***. Yeah &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://parentingteens.about.com/cs/marijuana/a/420meaning.htm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;420&lt;/A&gt;. I think thats pretty cool. 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/o2simcard.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;O2 SIM cards&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;600&quot;/&gt;

Well for now i will keep them. See what happens.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>2639</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-12 13:21:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-12 09:10:32</logtime>
<subject>Moonlight Sonata</subject>
<event>One of my favourite Classical pieces of music has to be Beethoven&apos;s Moonlight Sonata. I&apos;ve been saying for a few weeks now that i want to learn it, and hopefully buy the sheet music some time. 

Today i &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.mfiles.co.uk/Scores/moonlight-movement1.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;found it on the net&lt;/A&gt; and printed it out. I&apos;m determined to learn it!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>2926</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-12 13:50:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-12 09:16:34</logtime>
<subject>Low pay for Belfast!</subject>
<event>It would appear as though we have made the news! &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.theregister.co.uk&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Register.&lt;/A&gt; has an article on the research which was carried out recently by &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.investni.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Invest NI&lt;/A&gt; showing that Belfast &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/05/12/ni_it_wages/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;technology workers are some of the lowest paid in Europe.&lt;/A&gt; 

Only Bangalore in India, and Budapest and Prague in Eastern Europe, have lower salary levels.

The data also shows that IT workers in Dublin are paid dramatically more than Belfast workers, with wages coming in 27 per cent higher on average in the capital of the Republic of Ireland.

Possibly the most expensive city on Earth to hire IT staff is San Francisco, where a head of IT will earn some €165,331 per year, on average, compared to €91,251 in Belfast and €107,253 in Dublin.

Is this fair!?</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>3476</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-13 17:04:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-13 09:30:22</logtime>
<subject>White Label Rock!!</subject>
<event>Got to the Front Page just in time to for the sound check. They even sounded good then! They went on at about 9:30. Played 6 songs in total incluging 2 great instrumentals. Among the songs they played were Fire by Jimi Hendrex and Another Brick in the Wall (Part II) by Pink Floyd. Both of these covers were excellent! Amazing to listen to whilst stoned! They truly are a band whose name i will spread! I AM joint #2 Fan!!

Here are some great pics!

The band Strutting their stuff
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/DSCF0018.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Whitelabel&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

Ross
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/ross.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Ross&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;/&gt;

Johnny
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/johnny.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Johnny&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

Chris
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/chris2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chris&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;500&quot;/&gt;

Another pic of chris
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/DSCF0007.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Chris&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

The Band
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/whitelabel/band.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Chris&quot; height=&quot;540&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

More pics at my &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://uk.f2.pg.photos.yahoo.com/ph/philokane/album?.tok=phMUpGBB0WT6MqI2&amp;.dir=/fce0&amp;.src=ph&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Yahoo! Photo Album&lt;/A&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>3708</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-14 15:33:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-14 08:15:37</logtime>
<subject>Bye Bye NTL</subject>
<event>So i found out the other day that some guy from &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.bt.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BT&lt;/A&gt; had been round at the house and spoke to my dad. He managed to pursuade him to get rid of &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ntl.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NTL&lt;/A&gt; and &quot;go back to BT&quot;. I dont know what the guy said, but i would like to know. But its all good! I dont really care about the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ntlhome.co.uk/ntl_telephone/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NTL phone line&lt;/A&gt;, its the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ntlhome.co.uk/ntl_tv/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;channels&lt;/A&gt; (few as they are) and the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ntlhome.co.uk/ntl_telephone/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;NTL phone line&lt;/A&gt;, its the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.ntlhome.co.uk/ntl_internet/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Internet&lt;/A&gt; that i care about!

I think we will definately stick with NTL for the internet. &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/04/26/ntl_telewest_broadband/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The fact that they are increasing all the speeds&lt;/A&gt; is the main thing making me want to stay! According to the article on &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.theregister.co.uk&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;The Register&lt;/A&gt; they are increasing the 150k to 300k (thats me!), the 600k is to increase to 750k and 1mb moving up to 1.5mb, and all for the same price as before (except the 1mb which will be increased by £3)! 

Though they have strong competition from &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/business/3709949.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;BT who are reducing their prices by 70%&lt;/A&gt; and Telewest who are &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.theregister.co.uk/2004/04/26/telewest_broadband_cable/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;increasing their speeds and freezing their prices&lt;/A&gt; (which are less than NTL&apos;s!), &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://news.bbc.co.uk/1/hi/technology/3646825.stm&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;they are also going to provide the first 3MB connection in the UK!&lt;/A&gt;

This is all to happen in the summer!

As for the TV. We&apos;re getting &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.sky.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;SKY!!&lt;/A&gt; So im pretty happy about that! Apparently we&apos;re getting about &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.sky.com/skycom/packages/channel/0,,1,00.html&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;200 channels!&lt;/A&gt; 

Its all good!!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/smile.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smile!&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>3894</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-16 18:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-16 10:59:06</logtime>
<subject>Pesky Kids</subject>
<event>Today was my bro&apos;s birthday party. He and 7 of his friends went to the Ozone Lazer thingy, then came back here for food. I went down to grab some of the food, and make fun of them. They arent bad. Little rock n roll kids of today!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/bdaycake.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Chris&apos;s Birthday Cake&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>4320</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-17 19:17:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-17 11:28:27</logtime>
<subject>Its a GIRL!</subject>
<event>Just heard an hour ago that my auntie had her new baby within the last 2 hours or so. Its a girl. So far i dont know the name... 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/clipart/stork.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;stork&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>5313</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-19 00:06:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-21 08:47:51</logtime>
<subject>I hate computers... again</subject>
<event>So my parents computer decided it wasnt going to start up at all today. This meant that i had to reformat it even though i dont really have the time. I managed to get it done anyway. While Windowswas installing i setup the net on the laptop. Always got a backup method of connecting to the internet. Oh fun fun... maybe i should do some coursework now...

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/laptop&amp;comp.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;2 Computers&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>5108</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-20 16:15:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-21 08:39:00</logtime>
<subject>My Workspace</subject>
<event>Here is a pic of my Workspace at school. Oh the life i lead eh.

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/workspace.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;My Computer&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>4580</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-21 16:23:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-21 08:28:00</logtime>
<subject>Check out this for a water pistol! Afraid of water? Watch out!</subject>
<event>My brother just came home with this! One motherfucker of a water pistol!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/waterpistol.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Water Pistol&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>4676</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-21 16:29:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-21 08:32:08</logtime>
<subject>WOW look at my hand... yea i was bored... again</subject>
<event>Heres another crappy design i drew on my hand today in school. Ive been doin these things for years. Might get something like this done as a tattoo someday...

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/hand.JPG&quot; height=&quot;390&quot; width=&quot;580&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>5453</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-21 16:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-21 08:57:11</logtime>
<subject>What a mess!</subject>
<event>Damn my room&apos;s such a mess! I&apos;ll tidy it in about 2 weeks, whenever i finish school. I cant bloody wait until that day comes!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/bedroom.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;My bedroom&quot; height=&quot;450&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;/&gt;

Its a lovely day out - im gettin outta here, away from computer for 24hrs or so, thank god!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>5727</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-25 16:11:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-25 08:12:43</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=http://www.greatestjournal.com/quiz.bml?Q=183&gt;&lt;font size= 5&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;brown&quot;&gt;I AM BILL! (Snake Charmer)&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;font size=&quot;2&quot; color=&quot;brown&quot;&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://pictures.greatestjournal.com/userimg/845508/245741&quot;&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;
You&apos;re Bill!  I love you!  Anyways, you&apos;re skilled in the art of manipulation.  You&apos;re very strong, talented, powerful, and witty.  You don&apos;t seem to have any real sense of morality, and you only let your kindness show around a select handful of people (mostly Kiddo and  B.B).  You do have some regret for the horrible things you&apos;ve done, but won&apos;t let it interefere with your life.  You respect your opponents, and you generally believe in fair game.&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&lt;a href=http://www.greatestjournal.com/quiz.bml?Q=183&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;990066&quot;&gt;Kill Bill:  Which Deadly Viper Assassin Are You? (Vol. II spoilers... results with pics)&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/b&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>5962</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-25 20:41:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-25 13:43:43</logtime>
<subject>Christening</subject>
<event>Ethan William was christened at the weekend! Unfortunately, due to my own stupidity and not getting off work i missed the actually christening and quite a bit of drinking time. I got there at about 10pm, and quickly caught up with everyone ... well Helen was drunk anyway! I had the most fun i&apos;d had in quite a while, most fun with family, and the best part was it was all free!! Damn i want to get drunk again soon, havnt been drunk in ages, missed how good it feels (It feels even better when its free too). Here&apos;s some pics from the wonderful day!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/christening5.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/christening1.jpg&quot; /&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/christening2.jpg&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/christening3.jpg&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>6242</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-26 16:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-26 08:44:56</logtime>
<subject>Bond... James Bond (Or so it says on the box)</subject>
<event>Yesterday my brother got the new James Bond game for the PS2, &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.eagames.com/official/007/everythingornothing/us/home.jsp&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Everything or Nothing&lt;/A&gt;. It is completely different from the last one, &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.eagames.com/official/007/nightfire/us/home.jsp&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Nightfire&lt;/A&gt;, which was amazing! I havnt yet played it that much, but what i have played of it, and seen, i have really liked. It is apparently a lot harder than Nightfire, but it does look like it could be better. The graphics are definately better!

In multiplayer, two players can play co-operatively to complete a set of levels specifically for multiplayer. What i do like about this game is that it combines a lot of different types of play. For example, on many levels you are driving a car and others you are on foot. Thumbs Up to EA Games.

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/clipart/everythingnothing.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Everything or Nothing&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>6534</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-05-31 15:26:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-05-31 08:15:47</logtime>
<subject>Portstewart</subject>
<event>Oh My God! I had a great weekend… well not really a good Sunday anyway. Yeah, Friday was the same as ever, nothing exciting, movie and pool. Though the movie, The Day After Tomorrow was spectacular! 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/movie_posters/Day_After_Tomorrow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;The Day After Tomorrow&quot;/&gt;


Saturday went to town for a lunch and few drinks then went to work (turned out I was meant to be off work… but I stayed anyway so frustrated). 

Sunday, this was the day! We all went up to the house in Portstewart for the day. Got there at about 4:30 and immediately went for a walk down the promenade. We got some lunch then went for a walk to the rocks to smoke a few joints. That was good. We stayed out for a while, enjoying the dope and the company. After the BBQ and some T.V. we went out again. This time we went to the beach, to one of the largest sand dunes. The sun was immense, the heat was great, sand, sea and dope! It was truly wonderful, absolutely perfect. Lying back covered in sand… stoned! 

Its one of the best days I have had, ever! I feel so good now, I just want to do it again now. 

I know now that I *do* have friends! xox

Ethan, with personalised teddy
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/pstewartethan.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Ethan&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
