<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>41088</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-01 16:51:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-01 09:49:16</logtime>
<subject>Happy Aids Day</subject>
<event>I didnt smoke all day yesterday and havent so far today, nor am i going to. I opened a Student bank account and got freaked out by a friend saying he&apos;s watching the cameras here in the library. Im off to see what he&apos;s at, and get these 2 pints off him for talking to a random girl beside me...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>41303</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-02 14:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-02 06:42:35</logtime>
<subject>Cant say I didnt try...</subject>
<event>Got up at 12:30, went to class at 1:15. Class finished 40mins early. Went to Student Support, asked for nurse, nurse at conference. I try again tomorrow. 

I havent had a cigarette for a full two days. I dont feel too bad. There was a brief moment before i went to bed last night when i realisd and thought there was something missing, but other than thats it hasnt been too bad. I borrowed a few games from flatmate (Duke Nukem!), so my mind has been occupied. Although I had completely forgotten about work. What will I do when i get the urge to take a break and go for a smoke?? I dont know how I will cope. Its like a rule, I have to have at least one smoke break any time im at work. Ive always done it... Damn! I hope this works. Ive come so far (yes i consider two days quite far) I cant give in now!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>41628</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-03 16:27:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-03 09:02:42</logtime>
<subject>I feel trapped</subject>
<event>As much as i &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; loving it here, i have been feeling very trapped here in the last couple of weeks. Of course having no money has not helped at all. Its like being stuck at school. I cant run anywhere. I cant do anything. Cant go home, cant drink, cant go to the cinema... cant do very much. Things have just gone completely wrong. 

I was talkin to my parents on the phone last night. It didnt go well at all. I bought a pkt of cigarettes afterwards. I do however realise having done that that i dont want to smoke anymore at all and that I can do it. I had my last cigarette this morning and made a conscious decision that it will be my last. I really didnt enjoy that pkt very much. Two days without smoking has done me a lot of good, and so will the next many days to come. I just gotta find stuff to do in its place. 

work went ok without takin a smoke break. I got home, watched  
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0221027/&quot;&gt;Blow&lt;/a&gt; with directors commentary then learned about chemical reactions on &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/schools/gcsebitesize/&quot;&gt;BBC Bitesize&lt;/a&gt;. Then read, and stared into space for a while... at 6am I got up and watched GMTV and listened to the Chilis. I went to sleep at 8:30am and got up at 3:30pm. 

With much pursuation I have a little more money. I might treat myself to the cinema tonight...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>41937</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-04 23:28:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-04 15:53:38</logtime>
<subject>I wanna get drunk...</subject>
<event>I got home from work at about 10:40 and put on some great loud music and really wanted to be drunk and happy, its not fair! But I dont have enough money, and its too depressing just bein drunk in a room with only music (loud and great music of course). 

It really was stupid of me not to get the internet in a few months ago. I just cannot live without access to the outside world. Im too damn lonely and and have been feeling trapped (as mentioned previously) recently having to contend myself with all that I have in my room. I need to know whats going on. I need to be able to talk to people etc. Next semester will be so much different. 

I found out he other day that my one and only exam is on 11th Jan. Which means I will be free from 12th - 24th January! In that time I hope to spend much of it intoxicated! You are very welcome to join me!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>42333</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-05 04:20:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-04 20:26:16</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Its 4am and im still over at the uni on the net. Ive had a great time. Reading about blogs and of modern day journalism. &lt;A href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page&quot;&gt;Wikipedia&lt;/A&gt; - what a great invention


&lt;B&gt;Current Terror Alert Level&lt;/B&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/terror-all.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Terror Alert Level&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; src=&quot;http://www.geekandproud.net/terror/terror.php&quot; /&gt; &lt;/a&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>42523</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-05 12:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-05 04:36:51</logtime>
<subject>I Survived</subject>
<event>Once again, I didnt sleep. I stayed on the net (right here) until 4:30, then walked t0 24hr garage then back to room. Where I watched &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/blast/&gt;BBC Blast&lt;/a&gt;. Its a programme where they show lots of student short films. Lots of weird and wonderful storys, most pretty well made, all very inspiring. Then at 6am i started revising Java... Somewhere I along the line I got pretty lost and now I got a lot of catching up to do. The best thing is, I still havent had a cigarette in days! I really duno how I did it.

Right now though im waiting for the LRC (Learning Resource Centre) - library - to open. I need to make a flash intro for a movie for my (group) assignment for wednesday and I really dont know how to work flash and Im sick of reading the tutorial on the computer. Although its pretty good, and probably better than reading a book, I just dont really like my computer all that much. I need a new monitor and my mouse pisses me off...

Anyway, I decided I wasnt going to go to sleep cos i really wanna get up early on monday morning, and that definately wouldnt happen had I gone to sleep when I got in. So im gona try gettin a good bit more work done today (I would need to) then go to sleep early and do lots more tomorrow! YAY</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>42875</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-06 16:35:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-06 09:35:17</logtime>
<subject>Insert pseudo-intellectual title here</subject>
<event>Im actually feelin&apos; pretty good at the min. I got to sleep at about 10pm last night, and strangly woke up at about 12:30am, when i realised i went back to sleep again. Then I woke up at 8:20am to the anoying sound of my alarm clock, getting up at 8:40. Ive even got into a routine of trying to have breakfast every day. 

I sat in class from 9am until 3pm, having only one coffee break to sit with group in café and discus our assignment. The whole time i was working with Flash on the assignment. I didnt have a cigarette once - &lt;I&gt;even when offered!!!&lt;/I&gt;

When I walked outta my tutorial I actually felt pretty good. I feel that I could get a good mark in this module after all as our final movie looks pretty good and today I made a significant contribution so i should get full marks, in terms of individual weighting within the group. 

All I have to do now is revise for test tomorrow. Multiple choice. Hopefully I&apos;ll do ok - just worked it out! I only need ONE mark in this test to pass the module!! ONE mark!! SWEEEET! So after test tomorrow I have no more work to do! Other than working sainburys wednesday and thursday. Then im goin home on friday! Its been a month since Ive been home and I cant wait!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>43191</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-07 14:54:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-07 06:56:25</logtime>
<subject>Im a stupid cunt</subject>
<event>I was supposed to be in class at 9am this morning. I didnt sleep all of last night. But I managed to fall asleep at 8:15 this morning!! EIGHT-FUCKING-FIFTEEN!!! TWENTY MINUTES BEFORE I WAS GOING TO LEAVE!! I woke up at 2pm so very very pissed off!

The really strange thing is, I only started getting tired at 6:30am...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>43303</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-07 15:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-07 07:54:05</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/forum%20humour/google.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>44098</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-07 19:26:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-07 11:27:19</logtime>
<subject>I want a cigarette!</subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;Ive just come out of my final test for my programming module. It was fuckin tough. I got 48%. Shit, I know, Im just hoping its enough... &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Right now i really really want a cigarette. I was one of the last left to do the test. I hit the &apos;submit&apos; button with 01 seconds to go. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;December 7, 2004 5:11pm Quiz submitted&amp;nbsp; 59:59 00:01 &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I rushed some of the last questions, randomly selecting an answer for one or two. Looking over the test now and seeing the right answers against what I chose I think I got more right in the second half than the first. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Anyway, enough of that. Its over. Im not gonna worry about it. Im just gonna buy a packet of cigarettes and some alcohol!&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;Ever been called mean and thoughtless by someone you care for and think about a lot... It really doesnt feel good&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;IMG src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/traurig021.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>44384</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-10 01:10:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-09 17:22:15</logtime>
<subject>Home Sweet Fucking Home</subject>
<event>Its 1:11am and im over at the uni on the net while just about everybody else from &apos;The [Student] Village&apos; is getting drunk at the union. I was at work until 10pm and dont have enough money to go out never mind get drunk. I spend ages on the phone with my mum then arranging my weekend with ronan. I cant fucking wait to go home tomorrow. My dads comin&apos; to pick me up at about 12pm and we go for lunch or whatever. Its also his birthday tomorrow and having -£34 in my bank has meant that I havent been able to get him anything. I would like to go to town early and get something before he gets here but I doubt very much I will be able to get up early enough and I have no idea what to get him... 

When I get home I&apos;m gonna eat. Then Im gonna eat more. After that I may eat a little more. Then gonna go to the cinema with bro to see &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0317705/&quot;&gt;The Incredibles&lt;/a&gt;, which I&apos;m really looking forward to. Then gonna set up my computer and hopefully set the net up in my room. 

Anyone who I havent seen in we gotta meet up over xmas!! 

Only 16 hours to go!

P.S. 
I found out that I passed one of my modules! Got 47% Go me...!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>44647</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-10 09:13:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-10 01:22:22</logtime>
<subject>I have money!!</subject>
<event>There is money in my bank!!

Its 9am. I didnt sleep last night. I watched GMTV from 6 this morning, some cartoons, Everybody Loves Raymond (&apos;cos that show is great) and some other stuff. Dad&apos;ll be here at about 12. Im gonna get him a Birthday present in town... I have no idea what to get. He doesnt like anything...

I saw clips from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0367594/&quot;&gt;Charlie and the Chocolate Factory&lt;/a&gt; this morning. Looks fuckin awesome!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>44842</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-15 12:25:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-15 04:34:15</logtime>
<subject>Indie Rock And Roll</subject>
<event>Im just up 10mins. Im going to work in 15mins. Working 30 hours in total this week. I work on the deli counter and it changes between being pretty busy to being really boring. But its certainly nice being back home. I fuckin&apos; hate the store in Derry. 

I bought a DVD writer on sunday night, it arrived yesterday! I got it in and played around with it for a few hours, totally pissed off that I forgot to buy some blank DVDs after work yesterday, definately get some today, and if it works I will be renting some more DVDs later - also I wanna chat to hot girl in Xtra-Vision again...

I&apos;ve been home since Friday and Im enjoying being home - mum&apos;s still a bitch, but I ignore her most of the time. Havent done a lot really, trying to go easy on my money. Still havent bought anyone anything for christmas yet... I guess internet shopping could be out of the question at this stage.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>45227</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-15 21:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-15 13:09:32</logtime>
<subject>Meah</subject>
<event>Every get the feeling that if you died or (more likely) didnt communicate with anyone for a while many people wouldnt give a shit or wouldnt try contacting you? 


Didnt think so. 

I do....</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>45520</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-16 18:28:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-16 10:35:59</logtime>
<subject>40 hours</subject>
<event>Im just in from work and i feel really good. It feels strange. Work doesnt normally make me feel really good. Like I havent done anything other than work. My manager and I discussed the hours that I&apos;m going to do over the next 3 weeks and I&apos;m working just about every day. Starting with 40 hours next week. This has made me feel good... Im as confused as you are. Im working on the deli counter and I like it. Its easy. Im gettin the hang of it. People are nice. Manager&apos;s nice and I&apos;m gettin&apos; plenty of hours. I actually like working here, but fucking cant stand the store in Derry! Ive worked 6 hours a day for the last three days and it hasnt been too bad at all. Though Im doing 8 tomorrow and 7 on Saturday, then no less than 8 all of next week! Hopefully these 8 hour shifts will go ok. 

This of course means that I will be getting lots and lots of money! YEEEOOO!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>45651</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-17 23:38:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-17 15:55:49</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Went to Frames with Rachel and co. walked to Botanic and got a taxi from Fonacab. Ended up in taxi with chris&apos; ex-friend and mother of hot girl in my street, she was drunk too so it was ok lol. Anyway the bastard taxi driver charged us both the same far instead of charging us half cos we were goin to the same place! MOTHERFUCKER!!


Also realised that I can actually talk to ppl when im drunk! I like being drunk. Actually had an almost full conversation with lady who lives in my streen in the taxi - she was also a little drunk which helps. Remind me to drink more often.....</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>45984</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-18 11:40:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-18 03:42:01</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot;&gt;I got my hair cut&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>46328</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-21 00:19:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-20 16:25:17</logtime>
<subject>Smile Like You Mean It</subject>
<event>Sunday I did some shopping in town then called in to my granny on my way home, she gave me some money for christmas, which im probably going to spend on people&apos;s presents - oh the irony. 

Today I was working from 9am to 6pm. On my lunch break I listened to The Killers album in HMV on the headphones thingy for about 10 mins, I do love it! Then I came home feelin pretty happy for some reason, im liking working too - its strange. Anyway - I gotta go to sleep cos im gettin up at 8am tomorrow and dont wanna be as tired as I was gettin up this morning.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>46519</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-24 18:41:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-24 18:44:29</logtime>
<subject>Merry Fucking Christmas One and All</subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/fun/sk.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>46630</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-28 21:12:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-28 21:17:48</logtime>
<subject>WHY!</subject>
<event>So Christmas was good. Got drunk at uncles on Christmas Eve, stayed at home on Christmas Day, had quite a nice dinner. Went to Cousins on Sunday and got more presents - mostly HMV/Virgin vouchers - and got v. drunk with Helen. HEEEHEEEE Was lots of fun!! Then got home and went to bed. 

Monday morning i got up at 8am and went to work. I still felt drunk...

Recovered throughout the day.

Im working everyday this week. I have no time to spend any of my vouchers. I have no money. I have no friends... - yeah fuck it - im not goin any further. I was happy until about an hour ago...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>46897</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-28 23:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-28 23:35:15</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.quizilla.com/P/punkpirategal13/1067297738_cturesp131.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;You are totally obsessed. Your friends may find it weird at times..but you don&apos;t care, they have no idea what there missing!&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;YOU LOVE HIM YOU LOVE HIM YOU LOVE HIM!! DID I&lt;br&gt;MENTION YOU LOVE HIM!!!
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quizilla.com/users/punkpirategal13/quizzes/%20How%20much%20do%20U%20love%20johnny%20depp%3F%3F%3F(%20please%20rate%20my%20quiz!..AWESOME%20PICS!)/&quot;&gt; &lt;font size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt; How much do U love johnny depp???&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;BR&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>47198</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-12-30 18:21:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-12-30 18:25:06</logtime>
<subject>Jealous?</subject>
<event>Fuck... its the strangest feeling in the world - but it feels amazing! So i tell on person I&apos;ll go out with them on New Years Eve, someone else finds out and gets &lt;i&gt;jealous&lt;/I&gt;! I mean, seriously, jealous! I am shocked! Why would anyone be jealous of something to do with me! It makes me so happy, it truely does! I can not believe it. I feel loved! Just hope you can figure out what your doing lol! 

I love it! You have both made me happy!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
