<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>27818</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-02 19:10:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-02 11:28:08</logtime>
<subject>Savvy?</subject>
<event>Got home from work at about 1:30 last night and began to watch Pirates of the Caribbean again, determined to watch it all this time. I did watch it all, then proceeded to watch all of the special features on the other disc. Some very informative stuff about pirates. At 5:30 i walked the 10mins to the 24hr garage and got me some more cigarettes a pot noodle, super noodles, bread and milk. 

When i got back, finished watching special features, then watched the movie again, though i fell asleep half way through (at about 7:30am). 

Woke up at 5:30 and put the movie on again, this time from chapter 10 to the end. It really is a great movie and i do love Johnny Depp, i mean - what a guy, everything he says and does makes me laugh. 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/00327742_lg.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/poc007b.jpg&quot;&gt;

As for now, im in 24hr computer suite. Need to get some food soon, then probably gona go to the cinema to see Layer Cake - looks good.

I could have gone home this weekend, just like the vast majority of other students around me but I dont like to go home every weekend &apos;cos i love my freedom and independence, even if there isnt anything to do here by myself, but thats part of it, finding things to do. Learning to survive on my own, cos really, we are all alone, and if you can survive by yourself then your doin fine - thats my way of looking at it. 

Of course, if anyone would like to join me here some weekend, you&apos;re very welcome to do so, 

Damn its dark. It really wasnt that dark 20mins ago.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>28091</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-05 11:24:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-05 03:47:08</logtime>
<subject>Anyone?</subject>
<event>I fucking love being here, new life, new start, new friends, no parents and time to be independent and discover what i want to do with myself; live my life exactly how i want to and do whatever the fuck i want and have no one stop me. 

Though there is the odd time of loneliness, such as weekends. I dont want to do home every weekend because i like being on my own, i.e. away from my parents. I know it sounds like a bit of a contracdiction. But i know that if i go home every weekend i will just sit around at home and be bored... maybe it is a little better than being bored here with no one to talk to at all, but i dont have the freedom to do whatever the fuck i want when i go home. 

Yeah this is very strange i know... unless you do understand.

So last weekend i didnt go home and did spend a hell of a lot of time alone. 

On Friday night i was working until 1am. When i got home made some food and began watching Pirates of the Caribbean all night. I slept until saturday evening then i went to the cinema that evening. After the cinema I got some alcohol started drinking when I got back to my room. Alone. Obviously not something im going to make a habit of. I did get a little drunk, was listening to great music all night that made me feel really good. But i was lonely. I desperately wanted to talk to someone. Desperately wanted the internet so i could sit on msn. Sent a txt or two, with no luck in getting any replies. Generally feeling pretty depressed. 

Thinking of the few people that are close to me in my life, i mean, &apos;what-the-fuck&apos;??

I often feel that no one will ever be able to understand me. I am too jaded. I find it hard to converse with people because everything is a cliché and it annoys me. I all too often sit in a crowded room and say nothing because whenever someone does say something its always something stupid, that i probably could have said but thought it wasnt worth while. As Marilyn Manson said, &quot;There&apos;s nothing left to say anymore, everything&apos;s been said before.&quot; 

Okay so that&apos;s meant in a different context, but its the same idea. 

It does often come to my mind that i &lt;i&gt;could&lt;/i&gt; be anyone. Not to be fake or artificial, but when meeting someone for the first time i could be wild and crazy and say all manner of things that to other people may seem out of character, but i find it hard to do that. I have met a lot of new people lately, but havent been as different as i would have liked to have been. Yeah, everyone says &apos;just be yourself&apos; but when yourself doesnt get you anywhere you want to try something different. I try, and am gona try harder. 

If it doesnt work then i&apos;ll just go back to my usual silent, pensive, people-watching, forward-thinking, always thinking, never-talking sorta guy.

I&apos;ll let you know how I get on.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>28396</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-07 15:55:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-07 08:17:08</logtime>
<subject>Good start!</subject>
<event>Had class test for Programming module - in which im learning Java - Tuesday. It was done on computers, over a website set up by the university. 50 multiple choice questions, 50 minutes to do it. Whenever you  are finished you hit &apos;Submit&apos; at the buttom of the page and on the following page the mark is displayed. I spent the day before and morning before studying very hard. Going through all the notes we had been given over the last 3 weeks. It payed off. I got 81%. Surprisingly better than anyone else that i know!! Found out today that the average was 64%. So as you can imaging Im pretty damn pleased with that! 

Im still very confused by some stuff and although I did well in the test I cant even programe much yet, still a little behind with that aspect of things. But I got such a good grade by studying hard beforehand and Im determined to continue to read notes and keep up on stuff contuniously. 

Yesterday I decided not to go to lecture i had at 9am, instead i stayed in bed until 2:30. Went into town about an hour later, brought back something and changed something else. 

I tried to get my bank account upgraded to a student account but i was DECLINED! Im not pleased about that at all! Im only 19, I have have a job for 3 years always having money going into my account. Maybe its something to do with the fact that I would have about £200 go in every month then by the end of the month it would often be down to nothing... That could be the reason, and the fact that when i had my contract phone 2 years ago i didnt make payments on time twice... aw well, Im determined never to get a contract phone again so i wont have that problem again. Im also from now on going to go easy on my money. Ive upgraded my computer (though i still need to get a new monitor), Ive bought plenty of clothes, few CDs quite a few DVDs (Pulp Fiction, Eternal Sunshine of the Spotless Mind, Wonderland, Butterfly Effect, Good Will Hunting, Kill Bill Vol 2, I think thats it) and spent lots of money on radom crap. 

Im gona learn how to cook so that im not spending so much money eating every day, I will spend less on alcohol, when im drinking I will just buy a 1/4 of vodka - much cheaper than anything else! 

Etc Etc. 

Im going home this weekend and plan to just spend time with my family, parents and brother - whom i miss and know misses me.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>28439</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-11 17:21:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-11 09:21:27</logtime>
<subject>Well that was worth every minute</subject>
<event>I went home on saturday morning, arriving at central station at 1:30 - only to be treated like shit by my mum for most of the weekend. Mainly due to the fact that ive run out of money... and maybe she has some reason to be anoyed, but not to be such a fucking bitch about it all fucking weekend! 

So maybe i have spent a little too much money in the last 4 weeks, but not that much was a waste really. I did buy a printer, new mobile, new hard drive, have to pay part of university fees (which i will be getting back whenever my mum eventually pays em), and food and lots of drink etc. 

But being typically her, she just went on and on and on and on and on about it all weekend. This is exactly why i am so glad that ive moved out! I listen to her, a little, when shes around, and when im not near her i completely block her out and ignore it all, in a way. Yes i am going to be more careful with my money but i can learn this myself. I still have my loan to get, and im getting paid this friday, so i only needed to lend of money for a few days. 

On a lighter note, I went to the cinema to see Shark Tale, then met ronan and ronan for a few games of pool and couple of drinks. I went home at 10pm cos i was tired and wanted to spend some time in the comfort of my own house (obviously ignoring my mum). I just sat on the computer for a while and watched some TV. It was good. And i got to sleep in my own bed, which is a lot better than the one i have here, though this one isnt too bad. I also have nicer pillows at home and im going to bring one of them back with me next time im home. 

On sunday we went to grannys and... well didnt do anything that exciting really; watched friends (yay(!)). 

Got home, put clothes in dryer, went on computer, packed, moved TV from the landing outside my room into my room, so chris can enjoy it in there instead of in the landing where it can be heard and if mum&apos;s on the computer she thinks she can just call up every second. Its really anoying when you&apos;re playing games or watching tv/dvd. 

Got train at 9:15, arrived back at 11:30, got bus from train station to uni and walked from uni to halls. When i got in i unpacked and started to sort out some more of my stuff in preparation for puttin it all onto cds. Then played Burnout on PS2 with flatmate and this is turning into too much of a &apos;Dear Diary, today i did this then this then did a shit followed by...&quot; - you get the idea, its not what i was going for, never again.

Going to see HIM tomorrow!!!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/him.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>28924</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-13 00:02:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-12 16:10:14</logtime>
<subject>HE was FUCKING AWESOME!!</subject>
<event>Not long back from one of the greatest nights ever! 

HIM fucking rule!!

I also met drunken Pete - great guy! 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/DSCF0010.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/DSCF0011.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>29067</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-15 16:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-15 08:27:54</logtime>
<subject>My man!</subject>
<event>Just got email back from James. I do love hearing from him. It always makes me want to save loads of money and get my ass over to Rhode Island! But its hard to save. I dont have that much money available I dont really work more than about 15 hrs a week (doing 18 this week) wouldnt often get paid more than £300 and have a tendancy to spend a lot of money when i do have some. For instance - ive spend about £500 in the last 4 weeks. Plus im about to order a new monitor (£70) and im even contemplating new motherboard and processor... I just cant help it. I love my computer and use it everyday and i can never understand why its never as good as everyone elses. Then of course i like to go out occasionally, unfortunately i dont actually have that many days that i can stay out late/get drunk due to class hours. Then again that could be a good thing; save some money. And finally, i have to survive. I gotta feed myself now. Which i enjoy doing, i just gotta learn to cook stuff other than microwaveable stuff and sausages and waffles. I would give anything for a big stir fry... havent had one in years. 

If anyone has any ideas as to how i can live cheaply, and still survive and not fade away completely please, please bring them forward.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>29366</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-17 16:45:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-17 08:56:46</logtime>
<subject>Another one of those entries</subject>
<event>Could it be possible that i am incapable of showing affection towards members of the opposite sex? Im just too much of an outsider. I analyse things a lot and have many different interests from other people. I would consider myself to be smart and intelligent - whether you do or not - and im not very good at the whole acting cool and dancing in club shit. Everything is just filled with clichés and im not very good at that. 

So i got a girl that i dont know that well standing/sitting right beside me in club/flat what the fuck do i do? Make conversation i would assume - and talk about what, the fucking weather? Its just all so goddamn ackward! 

FUCK FUCK FUCK i hate it!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>29513</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-20 17:35:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-20 09:35:26</logtime>
<subject>Feel-Me Phil</subject>
<event>Damn it does feel good to walk into a room and have  10+ people call you name (Even if it is &quot;Sainsburys Phil&quot; or Feel-Me Phil&quot;). Last night i went over the one of the other blocks (friend in my flat has friends there) and we sat around for a while drinking, eating chinese and smokin pot. Then at around 10:30 we went to &apos;Frisco&apos;s Student Disco&apos; at the Carraig, it was better than i thought it would be. After a while in there, we moved on to Earth next door. It was also pretty damn good, a lot better than i thought it would be and not half as packed as i was expecting. After much drinking and dancing like an idiot we all left at about 2am. When i got out i found more people that i know. We walked back, and got stopped by police and told to keep quiet, then rachel started chattin to one of them and gave him a friendly slap on the chest and one guy said &quot;how many years for assaulting an officer&quot; and he said &quot;i&apos;ll let her off this time.&quot; I found it rather scary and funny. 

Got back and shifted between 4 flats (in 3 different blocks) for the next couple of hours, talkin to people, eating a pot noodle in someone elses kitchen, smokin pot and talkin to more people. 

I finally went to my own room and to bed at about 4am. Then i watched 2 Episodes of The Shield. During watching Dilly knocked on my door askin me for a lighter and said there was &apos;a session&apos; goin on but it was too late i was lyin in bed so i didnt bother. 

I woke up this morning at 9:30 and said &quot;fuck it&quot; and didnt bother going to class, instead i stayed in bed until 3pm. Then i got up got a shower had a bowl of Weetabix and left to go to the library. And here i am, at the library.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>29710</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-20 17:36:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-20 09:40:58</logtime>
<subject>More credit!</subject>
<event>On Saturday I had £10 credit
On Sunday it had gone down to £8.50
On Monday I had £10.50
On Tuesday I had £9.00 
On Wednesday I have £11.46

I have no idea why - but my phone credit has been &lt;B&gt;increasing&lt;/b&gt; over the last few days and i have no idea why. 

I am not by any means complaing - but quite freaked out.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>30095</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-21 15:17:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-21 07:43:11</logtime>
<subject>I love The Shield</subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;Last night&amp;nbsp;I sat up and watched &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.fxnetworks.com/shows/originals/the_shield/&quot;&gt;The Shield&lt;/A&gt; &lt;A href=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/B00009QNVD.jpg&quot;&gt;Season 1 DVD&lt;/A&gt;&amp;nbsp;until 5am. I fucking love the show so much, I just cant stop watching it. Im determined to watch all 4 disks by tomorrow. Im half way through disk 2 so im getting there. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;My phone credit has gone up again to&amp;nbsp;- fuck just checked again and its gone up even more than earlier. &lt;BR&gt;When i checked a while ago it was at £11.50 or so - now its at £12.09. This is insane but im not complaining!!&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Im off to eat then goin to work from 6pm to 12am&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;What you dressin up as for halloween?&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>30244</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-24 20:02:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-24 12:11:32</logtime>
<subject>Madison Avenue</subject>
<event>Ronan left 2 hrs ago for the train. We went to a bar called Metro. I even got into a conversation with a girl! She was a little older than I and I wasnt actually interested in pursuing anything. She had asked the guy that came over if he or anyone else could make a &apos;Madison Avenue.&apos; He came back a few mins later and said no. I then asked her what a &apos;Madison Avenue was and she told me and said she got it in belfast etc. Of course I forget now, then few mins later they went. It was interesting really. Maybe I could do it again... though can it be done without the help of drugs? 

Went home at about 11pm and watched The Shield all night. I got him hooked. 

I also spent a few hours tidying my room yesterday morning before he came, I even hoovered it too! Looked pretty damn impressive, now theres cans of coke all over the place - i may have drunk a little too much coke over the last week or so. Definately smoked too much - about 25 cigarettes yesterday! Im definately gona go easy on them for a while!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>30671</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-24 20:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-24 12:18:56</logtime>
<subject>&lt;&lt;~~Phone Credit Update~~&gt;&gt;</subject>
<event>Today I have £14.85 on my phone</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>30869</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-26 09:22:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-26 01:51:40</logtime>
<subject>RAAA!</subject>
<event>Im sick - im very fucking sick!! 

Too often am I in my room during the day and feeling very cold. 

Too often do i feel extremely tired during the day and occasionally sleep for a while.

Too often am i going out to drink and coming home between Sunday and Tuesday when I have class at 9am the next day.

Im sitting in practical class at the minute wishing that i hadnt gotten up this morning, its just not worth it. I could be getting some more sleep and not be too tired to revise for test i have later - which i really gotta revise for!

And on top of everything, this computer is being really gay and slow. 

Fuck it - im going!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>31219</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-27 20:25:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-27 12:37:34</logtime>
<subject>Too tired</subject>
<event>Ever get the feeling you&apos;re being ignored? 

A few &apos;friends&apos; of mine went to the cinema yesterday to see the orignal Alien. Although I&apos;m not really interested in it I said I would probably go. Later they called me to go to bar with them, they were on their way back from the cinema! I got some much-needed sleep, but the point is they went and didnt tell me. Ach I really dont give a fuck, they not lots of fun anyway. They live in the same flat and cant seem to do anything without the rest of them. As for me, im pretty friendly with some people, would like to be a bit more friendly with a few more people, but i do like doing things on my own - enough ranting.

Yesterday we went to Earth - it was pretty shit. I just cant stand dance clubs if im not drunk or otherwise intoxicated. I was just so tired from the night before. I had a 2 drinks and felt like shit. But i didnt want to leave &apos;cos i&apos;d spent a fiver gettin in. After a while we found some comfy seats and had a few more drinks, and a couple of hours later I wasnt feeling too bad. I mean seriously, you dont go straight from the cinema, or lying in bed as i was, to a club, you need to have a few drinks before hand!

I still havent decided what im doing this weekend. Im not sure whether im working or not on saturday, I&apos;ll find that out tomorrow in work. If I am working then i wont be going home, obviously. It shouldnt be as lonely around the halls this weekend as I know a lot of people are planning on staying to make the most of Halloween. But I just dont feel up to drinkin much for a while. I dont even know if i want to go out on Sunday (hallween night) &apos;cos i have class on Monday morning, a class i should really go to as i havent been to it for 2 weeks, and my &apos;group&apos; my feel im not taking part in the assignment enough, even though we have another 6 weeks or so to have it done. On top of that I dont have a great deal of money left this month (decided not to get the monitor yet). 

If im not working, then i will probably go home; I havent been home in 2 (maybe 3) weeks. But then I still cant decide whether i should come back early on Sunday for the halloween crap. Some sort of carnival/parade starting at 5 at the university car park, moving to the city centre for fireworks and DJs later. I just cant be bothered. Such a crap holiday - though not even a holiday for us student and I have to get up at 9am the next morning!! AHH!!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>31412</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-27 21:17:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-27 13:25:37</logtime>
<subject>On a lighter note</subject>
<event>IM GOING TO SEE GREEN DAY IN JANUARY!!!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/greenday.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>31698</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-10-29 18:08:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-10-29 10:15:05</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Yestserday I was almost pursuated to stay here this weekend, but then I remembered about my brother, and the fact that I havent seen him in about 3 weeks. I am going home early on saturday morning and coming back on sunday evening. In time to get drunk and see fireworks and the usual halloween shit - well im not gonna sit in on my own. 

I think ive got a cold, and Im starting work at 7pm until 1am. Gotta run. Need food too.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
