<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>31998</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-01 12:55:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-01 05:31:29</logtime>
<subject>Too much drink, too much money... and where has it left me?</subject>
<event>I have spent &lt;i&gt;far&lt;/i&gt; too much money lately! I bought drink yesterday, saturday and a couple of days before that. As well as drink I have done shopping, and I spend more money on food than I know I should. Right now I have less money than I should/need to last me until i get paid again in two weeks and any time now more will come out for dvds that I bought a few days ago and money came out in the last few days for services that I dont even use but havent bothered to cancel. Its just not working out. 

So going back a bit, I was really going to go home on saturday, maybe even come back again that night, but I &lt;i&gt;was&lt;/i&gt; going to go home. As it happened, I couldnt sleep (because I havent gone to sleep early in so long its hard to do it once so Im going to have to force myself into a routine), so at 6:33am I was still awake. I had watched a dvd, read a comic, started reading some of my new book, drew some crappy doodles, anything to keep me occupied until 7:am when I had planned to get a taxi to the train station - I realised that if I did go to sleep I wouldnt get up on time, so I didnt go to sleep. But then the worst thing happened, I woke up, looked at my clock and it said 12:35pm. &quot;Fuck, I fell asleep!&quot;

I was very annoyed. I was meeting Christine for lunch, I knew ronan would be pissed, not that I care that much whether he&apos;s pissed-off or not, but I do hate him yellin at me cos he&apos;s pissed at something I did, and I miss my bro and wanted to see him this weekend. Its been 3 weeks (I think) since I&apos;ve been home so Im definately going home next week - better not be working (I wish fuckin job would get my name on the fucking schedule so I&apos;d know which fucking saturdays Im supposed to be working!)

So I woke up at 12:35 and was really tired so didnt bother to move for about 1/2 an hour after that. Mum called, I told her how it happened, and she hung up on me again :(

When I got up I went into town with a friend and bought some make-up for &apos;dressing up&apos; and did a &apos;bit&apos; of shopping in Tescos. Then back to the flat to drink and... well i cant really remember what I did on saturday, oh yeah, just drank in the flat with friends, probably went out somewhere at some point. I was so pissed off - I drank quite a lot, but wasnt overly drunk, or as drunk as I probably should have been - I have a pretty high tolarance to drink and its so bloody annoying. I think my body takes an outsiders point of view/cynical attitude, as well as my mind, stopping me from getting very drunk and going very crazy/losing control often. I dont like it much, I just end up wasting a lot of money!

Yesterday, I got up at about 4, ate made myself up, a little, bought some more drink (which got lost later!) and headed to the ball in the union at 9pm, because I didnt have a ticket I wasnt very hopeful about getting in, so when I saw a friend heading in the opposite direction I went with him. We found some other friends who were heading to a bar in town. I went and didnt stay that long, I was tired and hungry and the music was shit. So I left at about 11:30 I think and got a curry chip at a chinese nearby. Then got a taxi back to the flat and drank for a bit with a friend... well he drank I was just fed up. They he proceeded to talk about fucking politics and gimme his fucking views and stories again and I really dont give a fuck, which I have told him before, but it seems its the only thing he can talk about. Its fucking annoying! 

I went to sleep at about 5am. Woke up at 12pm. Missed practical this morning. Have work to do for 4pm. I should get on with it, and get some food cos im hungry - more money! 

Although I didnt feel the effects of drink last night - I woke up feeling quite hungover...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>32179</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-01 20:01:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-01 12:07:43</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;B&gt;IT&apos;LL GET BETTER, RIGHT?&lt;/B&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>32476</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-01 22:56:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-01 15:06:21</logtime>
<subject>Is there a place?</subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;Im just back from the cinema. I decided to spontaniously go to see &lt;A href=&quot;http://imdb.com/title/tt0308644/&quot;&gt;Finding Neverland.&lt;/A&gt; The latest film staring Johnny Depp(!!) is just as good as any other, in terms of his performance anyway, the film was also very good. No really it was. A little tearful i was in some parts. I certainly feel a lot better myself having taken myself away from all that has been making me feel so down lately. It is nice to get away from things for a while. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;IMG src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/neverland6.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>32682</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-02 16:23:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-02 08:24:19</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;FONT size=4&gt;Insomnia&apos;s a killer&lt;/FONT&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>33241</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-03 08:54:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-03 01:02:30</logtime>
<subject>I didnt wake up with a hangover</subject>
<event>...and the only reason for this is that i did not sleep for a minute last night. Yes thats right, I havent slept at all. I was out last night at club donw the road and got quite drunk, spending yet more money. Then watched the election crap, played Age of Empires and decided not to sleep at all so I would not wake up with a massive hangover and as a result, not want to get up to go to class. So here I am at a computer at the university at 9am having not slept. I have a 2 hr class in 15mins after which I am going to go back to my bed and SLEEP! 

Here is a pic I took of me on halloween night. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/myself/Dscf0033a.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>33788</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-04 16:10:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-04 08:16:42</logtime>
<subject>68%</subject>
<event>I got 68% in test i did last week. Im really quite please with that as I was fearing the worst. 

I have an assignment to be in for tomorrow - which is not good, as i havent done a great deal for it. Im calling into work sick today so i can work on it. I dont feel too guilty about doing it as i havent been that well over the last week or so. 

Might also call in sick on friday so i can go home on friday night and spent 2 NIGHTS at home this weekend!

On another note - I joined the gym today! cost a tenner... that could have bought me cigarettes... or drink - but no, im gonna get fit!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>34022</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-05 11:58:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-05 04:13:14</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=2&gt;I dont have the internet in my room anymore&lt;/FONT&gt; &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;It was a unanimous descision. Apparently they value a few killobytes over &lt;EM&gt;my &lt;/EM&gt;education. The decided yesterday that it would be too slow to share a &lt;STRONG&gt;2MB &lt;/STRONG&gt;connection between 8 people, the bastards are leavin out the two of us who were connected using wireless network cables. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;It was nice while it lasted.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>34330</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-08 14:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-08 06:33:08</logtime>
<subject>All gone pear shaped...</subject>
<event>Its all fucked. I got blow at the weekend.

So I took off work &apos;sick&apos; on thursday and friday. Went home on friday. Went to the cinema on friday with ronan to see Saw (it was really good, twisted and intensly brutal and disturbing) then he stayed in my house. We watched movies until 6am then slept until 3pm. 

Please - dont ever let me let ronan stay at my house again!

Saturday night I got blow, then rolled a few joints and went to the cinema again to see Birth, really good, very strange. 

Got up at about 1pm on sunday - determined to hang out with my bro i took him in to town. We went to Forbidden Planet and bought a few comics and a HIM t-shirt and Queen t-shirt. Then back home. 

I got the train back to derry at 9pm, got in at 12 and went over the friends flat to smoke. I was really stoned. We watched Human Traffic. I was really stoned. 

Left at about 2:30 and went to sleep. 

I really should have gone to class this morning - but i didnt. Im gonna get kicked out of my group for this assignment cos i&apos;ve missed so many classes with em. It is pretty important. I have blow - but i cant smoke it until the weekend. Is that possible?? 

I now have to do Tutorial questions for 4pm. I have a test tomorrow I have to revise for too. DAMMIT, im fuckin this up. HELPP!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>34578</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-08 14:44:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-08 06:44:46</logtime>
<subject>All gone pear shaped...</subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;Its all fucked. I got blow at the weekend.&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;So I took off work &apos;sick&apos; on thursday and friday. Went home on friday. Went to the cinema on friday with ronan to see Saw (it was really good, twisted and intensly brutal and disturbing) then he stayed in my house. We watched movies until 6am then slept until 3pm. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;Please - dont ever let me let ronan stay at my house again!&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Saturday night I got blow, then rolled a few joints and went to the cinema again to see Birth, really good, very strange. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Got up at about 1pm on sunday - determined to hang out with my bro i took him in to town. We went to Forbidden Planet and bought a few comics and a HIM t-shirt and Queen t-shirt. Then back home. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I got the train back to derry at 9pm, got in at 12 and went over the friends flat to smoke. I was really stoned. We watched Human Traffic. I was really stoned. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Left at about 2:30 and went to sleep. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I really should have gone to class this morning - but i didnt. Im gonna get kicked out of my group for this assignment cos i&apos;ve missed so many classes with em. It is pretty important. I have blow - but i cant smoke it until the weekend. Is that possible?? &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I now have to do Tutorial questions for 4pm. I have a test tomorrow I have to revise for too. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;FONT size=4&gt;DAMMIT, im fuckin this up. HELPP!!&lt;/FONT&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>34994</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-08 17:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-08 09:36:15</logtime>
<subject>Fuck this</subject>
<event>&lt;FONT color=#CD853F&gt;Im off to smoke some pot&lt;/FONT&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>35283</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-09 15:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-09 07:37:04</logtime>
<subject>Gotta start somewhere</subject>
<event>Plans for this week:
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Tuesday&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Do exam&lt;BR&gt;Go to at least part of damn 3hr class that i havent gone to in about 4 weeks&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Wednesday&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Meet group and do the group thing and be really apologetic for my lack of participation up to now&lt;BR&gt;Study JAVA&lt;BR&gt;Go shopping&lt;BR&gt;I can drink today!&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Thursday&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Go to class at 1pm&lt;BR&gt;Study&lt;BR&gt;Go to work&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Friday&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/STRONG&gt;Dont stay in bed all day&lt;BR&gt;Do some studying&lt;BR&gt;Go to work&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Now lets see how this works out.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>35486</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-10 16:29:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-10 08:29:22</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;FONT size=6&gt;Weeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeeee&lt;/FONT&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/rasta.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/wave.gif&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/huepfen024.gif&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>35656</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-12 16:17:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-12 08:23:09</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>I&apos;ve done some of the stuff as mentioned in entry few days ago. Although i didnt go to class on thurs or do much studying... 

But i have only been out once this week, Wednesday - and it was a great night.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>35979</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-12 16:38:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-12 08:42:56</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>As i rule, i generally dont like these things and wouldnt normally put them on my journal. But occasionally it cant be a bad thing. I do like the way it says &apos;A Beautiful Mind&apos; as its my third favourite film at the min (after &apos;Pirates of the Caribbean&apos; and &apos;Good Will Hunting&apos;)

&lt;table style=&apos;font-family : Arial, Verdana, Helvetica, sans-serif; border-collapse: collapse; border: 1px solid black;&apos; cellspacing=&apos;0&apos; cellpadding=&apos;2&apos; align=&apos;center&apos;&gt;&lt;form action=&apos;http://memegen.net/viewmeme.pl?meme=1074626196&apos; method=&apos;POST&apos;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th colspan=2  bgcolor=&apos;#000000&apos;&gt;&lt;font color=&apos;#DDDD88&apos;&gt;Your True Nature &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;Username&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;&lt;input type=&apos;text&apos; name=&apos;armored_username&apos; value=&apos;obsolete_mind&apos; size=&apos;20&apos;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;The quality that most appeals to you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Sense of Humour&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;In a survival situation, you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Run like hell&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;Your hidden talent is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;A beautiful mind&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;Your gift is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Sexual prowess&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;In groups, you:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Get the party started&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;Your best quality is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Your protectiveness&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#333333&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #FFFFFF;&apos;&gt;Your weakness is:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td bgcolor=&apos;#DDDDAA&apos; style=&apos;border: 1px solid black;&apos;&gt;&lt;span style=&apos;color: #000000;&apos;&gt;Being predictable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;input type=&apos;hidden&apos; name=&apos;un&apos; value=&apos;llScorpiusll&apos;&gt;&lt;input type=&apos;hidden&apos; name=&apos;meme&apos; value=&apos;1074626196&apos;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=2 align=&apos;center&apos; bgcolor=&apos;#000000&apos;&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/table&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>36347</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-12 16:45:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-12 08:54:05</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Why the fuck did i only get paid £85 for a months work!! I have really been looking forward to today for the la st week or so as i&apos;ve run out of money. I was expecting £250-£300 but when ive only got £85!! This is a fucking outrage! Im working at 7pm (until 1am &lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/banghead.gif&quot;&gt;) so im going to march over to personnel and say &apos;YO! What the fuck&apos;s the matter wit&apos; you! I work hard all month and get squat! You should be ashamed of yourself! I quit!&apos;

Ahhhhh to quit sainsburys... &lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/boese076.gif&quot;&gt;

&lt;B&gt;*UPDATE*
It turns out that I have been using the wrong clock-in number in work, though i was never told i would have to use a new one, or given a new on for that matter, when i moved stores so its not my fault. But then it makes me wonder, how come i got paid right last month, and managed to get £85 this month? Did the computer just realise overnight that it didnt have the foggiest idea who the hell i was?</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>36604</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-13 15:04:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-13 07:05:03</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot;&gt;Im off to Bangor&lt;/font&gt;&lt;br&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>36632</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-13 23:35:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-13 15:41:39</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>I got home at 2pm, told chris we were goin out and got mum to bring us down to the train station, then told chris we were goin to bangor for the (rest of) the day. Got there and walked around a bit, looked at some shops, i bought a t-shirt or two, we walked some more, had lots of fun with the 2p machine (the one that slides in and out and the money falls down) then moved on to the oh so hard core 10p slot machine, spent a pound and won a pound. Then we walked around some more, got a pizza and chips, walked to a bench to eat said pizza and chips, and walked some more, and once more for luck. Caught the train back again at 7:20, got lift home and... I went and smoked a joint while chris played Age of Empires then i watched Bridget Jones&apos; Diary. Now I&apos;m going to play Age of Empires and drink a can of coke.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>36955</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-15 16:10:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-15 08:17:28</logtime>
<subject>I&apos;ve Fucked up</subject>
<event>I have no money. Yes the bastards at work arent going to be able to give me the money until at least thurs. I think the guy was even implying that they shouldnt really cos it was &lt;I&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; mistake. I should think not. If i had been told to use a different clock-in number i would have used it, but i wasnt told nor given one so how the hell is it MY fault. FUCKERS! Now i have no money - apart from the £7 i managed to find out of mostly 20ps in my room. &lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/smilies/sad-smiley-047.gif&quot;&gt;

&lt;B&gt;*UPDATE*
Thanks to a good friend - i now i have £20 in my bank - i make it last until thurs (when i &lt;i&gt;better&lt;/I&gt; get my money from work!)&lt;/B&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>37183</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-20 20:58:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-20 13:03:19</logtime>
<subject>I dream of... Age of Empires?</subject>
<event>&lt;P&gt;Yeah most people may dream of... well whatever you dream of, but last night - actually i think it was more this morning - i dreamt about Age of Empires, you know, the game: 
&lt;P&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/package.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;P&gt;My alarm went off at about 2pm and i hit the snooze button so many times every 9 minutes after it went off again and suddenly i realised it was because i didnt have enough food that it kept going off so i collected more food and and the alarm stopped going off. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;It was wierd. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;I havent been on the internet in ages. &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Sainsburys did give me some money, but on just last night, and only £40. The bitch said she owed me only £90 but i think it should be about £160. But she couldnt even give me back the whole £90, no she only gave me £40. So i had to phone my mum to ask her for some... &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Its not going well at all on the money side of things either... &lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;Im beginning to see what its like not having any money. I gotta survive another 3 weeks unitl i get paid again... or sell something on ebay...&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;In all, i havent done much over the last few days. I went out on wednesday to the union. Worked on thursday and worked on friday. On days that im working i never seem to do anything else, even though i dont start until 6 or 7pm. I just sleep until about 2 hours before i gotta go to work. Then come home watch tv and smoke lots...&lt;/P&gt;
&lt;P&gt;If anyone has any suggestions for ways i could make some money please share them. &lt;BR&gt;Any donations will be greatly appreciated. Please send to &lt;A href=&quot;mailto:philipokane@ntlworld.com&quot;&gt;philipokane@ntlworld.com&lt;/A&gt; via &lt;A href=&quot;http://www.paypal.com&quot;&gt;www.paypal.com&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/P&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>37417</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-21 21:09:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-21 13:05:52</logtime>
<subject>The microwaves broken</subject>
<event>One of my flatmates told me last night that the microwave in the kitchen is broken. I used it earlier anyway. I didnt feel so good for about 20 mins after i ate this normally extremely yummy meal. 

Today i got up at 4pm. Watched tv for a bit then went to sainsburys. Bought hair gel, sleeping tablets and spaghetti carbonara and tobacco. Back to the flat - smoked a joint and out again. This time i remembered to post the letter i should have posted a week ago! Sent reciept for mum to bring something back for me and Nightwish&apos;s Once album for my bro and Age of Empires cd. 

Lately ive just been smokin and watchin tv/dvds. Nothing too exciting and i expect it will be like this for the next few weeks until i get paid again. Im also gonna run out of dope in that time... I&apos;ll find some way of coping im sure. 

Ive done a lot of thinking over the last few days... cos thats what happens when u smoke dope for hours on end alone. I have made out a few plans for myself. A budget, Im gona make daily plans, maybe, and try to keep to em, so i study when i should etc and dont forget to do everything. 

On a lighter note - we got a new iron. Im going to do some ironing soon, and enjoy it. Ive only ironed twice since i got here. 

More crap same time next week</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>37682</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-21 22:31:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-21 14:42:04</logtime>
<subject>How clean is soap?</subject>
<event>Ive been thinking about this for a few weeks now. &lt;i&gt;How Clean is Soap?&lt;/I&gt;

So you touch the ground, house, car, banisters on stairs, your body, &lt;I&gt;soap&lt;/I&gt; etc. Then turn on the tap rub your hands around the soap bar for about 20 seconds then rinse and dry. All clean and ready to be put in ur mouth if or eaten off? 

I want clean soap!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>37930</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-22 20:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-22 12:47:33</logtime>
<subject>Today I bought soap</subject>
<event>Well i thought about it, due to the fact that i only got up at 3:30pm and I have no money, I did not buy soap. But i did think about buying soap. 

One of the worst things thats been happening to me lately is not being able to sleep. Insomnia. Last night i was tossing and turning, listening to music, i read, watched The Shield (but that could never make me sleepy), smoked a few joints, the usual - but nothing worked. I finally got to sleep at about 5:30am. I was supposed to get up at 8am this morning. I only woke at 9am, which was strange cos i set my alarm for 8am - just proves that if im rea lly tired i can sleep through the alarm for an hour. Even though I bought some crappy sleepin tablets in sainsburys - they did no good at all. I know the same is going to happen tonight cos im just not tired and wont be for hours yet...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>38296</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-22 23:12:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-22 15:25:27</logtime>
<subject>Clinical Depression eh</subject>
<event>Just been talking to my mum over msn, for the first time ever - feels weird. Being how i really am etc. 

So anyway, ive been telling her that i havent been sleeping lately. I want her to post some melatonin to me, but she&apos;s reluctant to do so. She also diagnosed me with Clinical Depression. Amazing. Could very well be true.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>38421</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-23 17:58:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-23 10:06:25</logtime>
<subject>Its all go!</subject>
<event>&quot;Hell yes!!!&quot;

&quot;Dude this will be fucking great!&quot;

&quot;Now look, you got me all excited.&quot;

Those were the words of James. As of today, I am going to America this summer! 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://www.inquiry.net/images/flag6-50.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>38761</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-24 17:27:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-24 09:36:06</logtime>
<subject>It didnt work</subject>
<event>No matter how hard I tried, I just couldnt go to sleep. It was between 5:30 and 6am that I finally managed to get to sleep. I woke up at 1pm to the most irritating music from the guy in the room next to me. It was the most unbearable pop crap ever. But no matter how many times i tried to get up, i just couldnt do it. I did however get up 3 hours later. It was hard. My head hurt. I felt really sick, still dont feel great, but im up, isnt that the main thing? Im in the library and i have been considering doing some &lt;I&gt;work&lt;/I&gt;! Yup i brought my Java text book and an exercise book and im going to go down to the desks and try learning some stuff.

Last night at about 7pm i was asked by one of my flatmates if i wanted to go out. Of course i want to go out. But i couldnt, cos ive no money. Later i went to the shop at 11:30pm and 15-20 were walkin down the road as i was walking back one after the other many of them called my name sayin why i wasnt goin out. Its a nice thing to happen. I just wish now that i have some friends i had money to go out... 

I just know tonight is going to be exactly the same. Im trapped.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>38976</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-25 14:06:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-25 06:14:35</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>I managed to get up today at 12pm. On time for class at 1pm. Now on break between class. Gotta go back. 

Although I got up earlier than i have in a while and wasnt too tired when i woke, i didnt get to sleep until 6am. I was lying down at 1:30 after reading and playing with my belly button. But then I got bored and really into the book. It felt like I&apos;d stopped a film half way through, so i read a bit more. Then played Snake on my phone and got 1115, then watched some skiing on 4 then tried going to sleep again. Eventually I did. Today im working until 12am. Hopefully i will be tired when i finish and be able to sleep soon after.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>39327</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-26 17:44:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-26 09:49:28</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;FONT size=5&gt;&lt;STRONG&gt;Boys Dont Cry&lt;/STRONG&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>39457</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-26 18:05:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-26 11:50:30</logtime>
<subject>Ronan got a job!!</subject>
<event>I was woken up this morning by a phone call from ronan. Well it wasnt morning, more like 2:30. He got me up which was good. I was working until 12am last night and was going to go straight to bed when i got in, but i decided to get really stoned instead. I went to sleep at about 6am. 

So it turns out he&apos;s finally got a job. Yeah, we thought it would never happen, but it has. He starts on monday. £4.20/hr. He&apos;ll have lots in no time. Maybe even more than me, cos right now I have ... about £2, and no more. Im gonna have to ask mum for more. I really dont wanna do that. This isnt good. Not good at all. 

Im going to die out here and ive got no one to help me...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>39711</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-29 08:47:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-29 00:52:40</logtime>
<subject>No rest for the wicked...</subject>
<event>Once again I didnt sleep last night, at all. Between tossing and turning, reading and playing Snake on my mobile i just couldnt do it. After a while I realised there wasnt much point. If i did manage to get to sleep, getting only 2-3hrs sleep i would never manage to wake up again. 

So now im in class ready for another day. Oh, Joy(!)</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>40108</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-29 16:57:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-29 09:00:47</logtime>
<subject>My heart&apos;s beating too fast...</subject>
<event>Just back from talkin to the course director... It was scary. 

Im gonna go see doc tomorrow. Its gonna work out... right.

Its been 25hrs since I last slept. I gotta sleep. Im tired. Im gonna go to bed within the next two hours and hopefully sleep through to tomorrow.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>40347</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-30 15:55:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-30 08:09:20</logtime>
<subject>Today i sharpened a pencil</subject>
<event>I was pretty tired when i got back to my room yesterday. I watched a bit of tv, read some of my book, studied a little and ate a pizza. I was asleep between 10:30 and 11pm, im so proud. I got up this morning at 10:30am. Its not as early as it should be but its a hell of a good start. I was going to go to sleep at 8 or 9pm, but i got hooked on tv. I dont like tv. It cures my boredom, but i find that im just watching so much crap and wasting so much time. 

I am really considering getting the internet in my room next semester. Ive gone a little (huge understatement) nuts with money this semester, and I have had very very very little (litterally living on less than £2 a day) over the last two weeks. This was due to that fact that I had spent all my money and wa s relying on my pay. But sainsburys fucked up. I was forced to call my mum yesterday and (literally) beg for some more money. Just checked and she very kindly put £20 in my bank. I can now live for another few days. 

I did sharpen a pencil today. Havent done that in about 2 years... It felt good.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>40794</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-11-30 20:35:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-11-30 12:50:08</logtime>
<subject>I quit smoking...</subject>
<event>Today, until the time that i next have money/have a drink/someone offers me a cigarette i officially quit smoking.

Its gonna be tough, but its for the best, probably. Apart from the fact that I only have £20 to last me until next week, as well as train ticket home - okay thats asking a bit much outta £20, but the point is I have very little money and just cant afford it.

So I need to think of things to keep me occupied during the day. I do have a very short attention span. Which is why I was considering getting a games console. Although if i had the internet that would solve so many problems. I could refrain from smoking, not watch tv, be able to get more music, it would be academically benificial. Its a tough call, &apos;cos it is quite expensive - but its been very hard without it and ive only been here 3 months. Another 5 months like this and I think im likely to go completely nuts!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
