<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>24599</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-06 02:15:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-05 15:44:42</logtime>
<subject>Disneyland</subject>
<event>So i&apos;ve been lazy lately and not bothered to update this - but i want to and am definately going to do it now!

We got back from Paris on Wednesday. I great 6 days! 

We left on Thursday at about 12. Arrived at about 4pm. Got coach from the Airport to Disneyland. I knew we had arrived when i saw the first huge hotel, then the rest soon after - they are massive! We arrived at ours eventually. The Kryiad was the hotel we stayed at. Very nice, very big!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF03301.jpg&quot;&gt;

The first night we just took the bus from the hotel to the Disney Village (free entry area with clubs, bars, restaurants and shops), just took a look around the place. 

The next day we got up early for breakfast at 9am. This consisted of a few croissants, yoghurt and another bread type thing or two.

On the first day we went to the most recent of the two Parks: Walt Disney Studios.

Disney Studios was great. Lots of special effects, rides and adventures into the world of Disney, that sorta stuff. The weather was amazing which added to it all!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0176.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0111.jpg&quot;&gt;

I went on the Aerosmith Rock &apos;n Roller Coaster - which was amazing. I dont usually do well on rollercoasters, but this was great. It lined up and counted down from 3. Then it went off at high speed into the darkness. The track went all over the place in what seemed like a very small room in almost complete darkness with the occasional bit of blue and silver track. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0094.jpg&quot;&gt;

Next we went on the Armageddon (special effects) thing. It was... well not that good really, just a room that shook around, a few flames and lots of smoke. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0097.jpg&quot;&gt;

Next was the Studio Tram Tour. This tour brought you round the back area of the park. Some very nice effects, shown here! 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0133.jpg&quot;&gt;

One of the best shows was at the Moteurs Action Stunt Show.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0095.jpg&quot;&gt;

THis included some nice explosions and fireworks:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0091.jpg&quot;&gt;

Later we caught the 3pm Studios Parade. 

Goofy prancing around:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf0156.jpg&quot;&gt;

Tinkerbell
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf01511.jpg&quot;&gt;

Mickey and Minnie Mouse
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0168.jpg&quot;&gt;

Donald Duck
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0162.jpg&quot;&gt;


On Saturday we headed straight for the main Park
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0208.jpg&quot;&gt;

The Main Entrance
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0209.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0335.jpg&quot;&gt;

Went on Big Thunder Mountain - surprisingly not as scary as I was expecting - but fun all the same!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0298.jpg&quot;&gt;

We took a nice boat ride around part of the park. Unlike the Tram, nothing exciting happened at all.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf03061.jpg&quot;&gt;

Later we caught the evening parade and fireworks display:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/Dscf02471.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/disney/DSCF0290.jpg&quot;&gt;


Overall - I had a great time at Disneyland, i just would have preferred if we had stayed for only 2 days and not 3 as we had really seen most things by the 3rd day and i was pretty bored of it and desperately wanted to go on to Paris.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>24877</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-07 21:15:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-07 13:16:50</logtime>
<subject>Gaye Paris</subject>
<event>So on Sunday 29th August we packed our stuff and placed it in the safety of the hotel while we went off for our 3rd and final day of Disneyland enjoyment. 

After a few hours of wandering around the park on my own trying to take it all in while my dad and and bro went on the Pirates of the Carribbean ride again (for the third time) we finally went back to the hotel to get our stuff and then to the train station. 

Off the train and onto the appriate metro line to the nearest station from the hotel. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/Dscf04051.jpg&quot;&gt;

Hotel Novanox. It wasnt as good as the one in disneyland, or as big by far - but it was still nice and the people who ran it were pretty nice. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0354.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;

On the first evening i didnt bring camera. We went to the Eiffel Tower, which looked amazing all lite up.

The next day we got up early for breakfast and headed out to Notre Dame. Just a huge cathederal really - very nice on the inside! No flash photography they say.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/Dscf03601.jpg&quot;&gt;

The huge stained glass window inside the church:
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/Dscf0372.jpg&quot;&gt;

Later we went to Eiffel&apos;s Tower - this time went up it, right to the top!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0451.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;360&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0446.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;360&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0445.jpg&quot;&gt;

What a view
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0465.jpg&quot;&gt;

Later we took a boat trip along the River Seine - which is where i took this pic from
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0524.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;360&quot;&gt;

One of the beautiful bridges along the river
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/Dscf04981.jpg&quot;&gt;

Day two - We left the hotel at about 11 and I went around on my own until meeting the parents again at about 4pm. I went to a History Museum and tried to go the Picasso Museum but it was closed on Tuesdays - really anoyed at that. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0536.jpg&quot;&gt;

Hotel de Ville - I love the buildings in Paris - everyone is so spectacular!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/Dscf05451.jpg&quot;&gt;

Moulin Rouge
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0012.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;

Finally - The Lourve. Unfortunately we didnt get to go in as it was closed when we went and this was on the final evening. Such a beautiful place!
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0041.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0048.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/paris/DSCF0051.jpg&quot; height=&quot;480&quot; width=&quot;640&quot;&gt; 

Yes i had a great time and will definately be going back!!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>25213</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-08 14:53:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-08 07:10:13</logtime>
<subject>Goodbye Dear Nilfisk</subject>
<event>I just did the hoovering for the final time before i move out!! 

I will miss this thing...
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/random/nilfisk.jpg&quot;&gt;



.... not</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>25529</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-12 23:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-12 15:24:03</logtime>
<subject>Last Night</subject>
<event>This is my last night in this house for a week. Then after next weekend i prob wont be home for about 2 weeks. Im moving to Derry tomorrow, and yes i am bloody excited! 

Gona be getting up at about 8 to put everything in the car and hopefully leave before 11am. When i get there im gona unpack for a bit then go for lunch with the parents, do some shopping then send them off on their way, as quickly as possible. Then i plan to sit in the students union bar for the rest of the night!

I keep y&apos;all updated. Im very much lookin forward to this! 

Finally - out of the house. My own boss, so to speak. No one to tell me when to come home, when to go out, when to tidy, wash, go to bed, not to smoke in the house etc. Should be good!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>25652</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-16 16:47:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-16 08:48:18</logtime>
<subject>UNI&apos;s fuckin Great!!</subject>
<event>No Time - more in a couple of days!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>25945</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-21 14:14:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-21 06:21:38</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Its Friday afternoon at 2:30 and ive just gotten up. Had a great time here since i moved on thurs. I had a nice advantage having met a couple of people on the internet (newstudent.org) and talked to them online then met up when we arrived on monday. 

I arrived at about 12pm, went to the registration office to sort some stuff out then over to accommodation office to pay then to the halls to get key and move in. The room is great, got my own en suite too!

After doing some shopping with the parents I met two guys from the net and sat and drank for a bit. Later we went to a local bar. 

The next day i got up at 9am and finished unpacking and tidying my room, this took about 2 hours! Later i drank some more.

Wednesday i did some more drinking.

On thursday i enrolled. Had to find the Sports Hall, get a photograph taken, go somewhere else to enroll on computers, go somewhere else to sort out fee payment and get my ID card laminated. 

Afterwards I called ronan who told me he was gettin a lift and would be here in about an hr.

A while later he arrived blah blah blah.

Later we were informed of a party in one of the other blocks. We went at about 8. There were only girls there at first, which i wasnt complaining about. After a while it picked up. Was a good night. Ronan certainly enjoyed himself! I got a nice call from him at 9am askin me to let him in!

Later on that day (friday) we went to the cinema to see Open Water which was unconventional but very good. Then to a couple of bars, found a great alternative hang-out; &apos;Bound for Boston.&apos; Live Music and pool tables! 

Well its 18:04 on sunday now and Ronan left an hour ago - thank god! Such an asshole at times! He certainly wont be round here that much i&apos;ll tell ya that! Well im bored... gonna give someone a call i think and see about doing something the rest of the night. 

My Room
[IMG]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00091.jpg[/IMG]

[IMG]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00111.jpg[/IMG]

View outside my room
[IMG]http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00121.jpg[/IMG]</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>26112</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-21 14:22:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-21 06:24:45</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Its Friday afternoon at 2:30 and ive just gotten up. Had a great time here since i moved on thurs. I had a nice advantage having met a couple of people on the internet (newstudent.org) and talked to them online then met up when we arrived on monday. 

I arrived at about 12pm, went to the registration office to sort some stuff out then over to accommodation office to pay then to the halls to get key and move in. The room is great, got my own en suite too!

After doing some shopping with the parents I met two guys from the net and sat and drank for a bit. Later we went to a local bar. 

The next day i got up at 9am and finished unpacking and tidying my room, this took about 2 hours! Later i drank some more.

Wednesday i did some more drinking.

On thursday i enrolled. Had to find the Sports Hall, get a photograph taken, go somewhere else to enroll on computers, go somewhere else to sort out fee payment and get my ID card laminated. 

Afterwards I called ronan who told me he was gettin a lift and would be here in about an hr.

A while later he arrived blah blah blah.

Later we were informed of a party in one of the other blocks. We went at about 8. There were only girls there at first, which i wasnt complaining about. After a while it picked up. Was a good night. Ronan certainly enjoyed himself! I got a nice call from him at 9am askin me to let him in!

Later on that day (friday) we went to the cinema to see Open Water which was unconventional but very good. Then to a couple of bars, found a great alternative hang-out; &apos;Bound for Boston.&apos; Live Music and pool tables! 

Well its 18:04 on sunday now and Ronan left an hour ago - thank god! Such an asshole at times! He certainly wont be round here that much i&apos;ll tell ya that! Well im bored... gonna give someone a call i think and see about doing something the rest of the night. 

My Room
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00091.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00111.jpg&quot;&gt;

View from my room
&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/blog/Dscf00121.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>26447</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-21 14:27:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-21 06:54:59</logtime>
<subject>The Bunker</subject>
<event>So yesterday was my first day of classes. Up at 9:15 for first class. Got in and the lecturer simply said, &quot;Anyone who doesnt have a seat come back in an hour.&quot; As it happened i did have a seat. He just showed us his website where we can get information on all the modules, he also puts up work and assignments on the net. He also gave us all our usernames and passwords for the network. Mine didnt work. An hour later he let us go, then i went to the library for a while. At 3:15 we had a course induction for the whole faculty (of engineering). This was taken by the course co-ordinator. He basically went through all the rules, regulations and structure of the year and courses. 

After that we were given a talk by the people in charge of the Halls and went bowling with everyone from the halls. It was quite good, plus we got free food!

We got back at around 9pm then went to the students union bar shortly after. There was a &apos;disco&apos; on later. THe doors to the other bar opened at about 11pm i think. The night started out with me going to the bar to get some drinks, only to find some nice girls sittin at our table. Got chattin to them and their friends came and more of our friends came and more (cheap) drink was bought and it was a great night! 

Then i hit my head on the wall as i rushed to get up from my bed to go the toilet. Hopefully this red mark on my forehead wont turn into a bruise.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>26671</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-22 15:04:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-22 07:10:16</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Today i ate a banana! 

Then i went to class for 2 hrs from 9am, got hair cut, bought nail varnish remover, phoned BT, watched some TV and here i am. Later i got class from 5-8pm: algorithmic programming!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>26917</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-27 12:38:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-27 04:44:22</logtime>
<subject>Home Sweet Home</subject>
<event>I got the train at 11:25 and arrived at central station at 1:30. Mum picked me up and i went with chris to Forbidden Planet and spent £10 on commics. Then went home, got food and went out with ronan. First we went to Laverys and played some pool then to the Front Page and saw three really crap bands; Fool, The Dangerfields and some other band. Eventually after spending 45 minutes trying to get a taxi we finally got one. That morning i woke up. Went to Lisburn with ronan and his mum to get him a new digital camera. Then on to grannys for the usual family gathering and lots of drink. At 9pm i got train back to Derry again. 

I brought some clothes with me to get washed, but the damn dishwasher was broken. Then my dad managed to fix it on sunday but it was too late &apos;cos i wasnt home at all on sunday. I also forgot to bring my new 160GB hard drive back with me. Gonna get mum to post it i think, cos i wont be going home next weekend and i cant survice 2-3 weeks more without it.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>27330</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-27 16:12:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-27 08:15:08</logtime>
<subject>Oops</subject>
<event>Dad caught me smokin outside my granny&apos;s house on sunday! He was up the drive way and i was with rach on the street. He called me just as i had the cigarette in my mouth and he saw it. I walked up to him and he gave me a really angry look and said, &quot;Don&apos;t ever let me catch you doing that again!&quot; I doubt he will tell my mum and hopefully wont mention it again.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>27632</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-09-30 15:59:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-09-30 08:09:20</logtime>
<subject>On behalf of the class...</subject>
<event>Woke up this afternoon at 1pm, class at 1:15 - hugely hungover!

Tried watching Pirates of the Carribbean again last night when i got in. Got about 3/4 of the way through. 

Today i became Class Rep. Hopefully it wont be too demanding, Christine says i will crack under the pressure but i can handle it. 

Working tonight 6pm - 12am. Im really really tired now i dont know how im gona cope in work so long and so late i may have to do something about these hours soon.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
