<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>6705</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-01 19:04:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-01 11:28:01</logtime>
<subject>Its fuckin great weather... and im sitting here</subject>
<event>What the fuck! the weather is fuckin awesome at the minute. My room is really bright, i can see through my window that its really sunny outside... but im sitting here, infront of my computer! Once again today in school i said i would do a lot of work at home... nope. When i got home, 3 hours ago, i said i would definately go out a while later. Im still here!! Still reading the news, Listening to music, on the usual forums, downloading trailers, reading about new movies etc... but im not outside where i should be!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/bedroom2004_0601.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bedroom&quot;/&gt;

I even rolled 2 joints for myself earlier... havnt smoked them yet. Maybe, maybe i&apos;ll roll another one or two, maybe that will get me to go outside. My mouse (cordless optical) seems to not be working very well at the min, maybe that will get my off the computer for a while. [UPDATE - restarted computer and got mouse working again]

I just cant help it, i love it so much. I mean... here i can do whatever the fuck i want, to an extent. I listen to music, talk to people, and in general read about stuff... useless crap that will not further me at all? No i dont think so, i believe that all i do on the internet/computer will help me in some way. Whether or not i spend shit-loads more time online than others i dont care, its just a slightly different lifestyle. I dont watch tv all day, play football, drink, smoke, hang around the street corner or local shop, i learn. Read and educate myself. 

Right, im getting my shoes on now... just as the sun disappears slightly :(

Out into the real world i go on a tuesday of all days! Wish me luck

[UPDATE - An hour later im still here. As soon as i finish typing this however im leaving, off to smoke a joint!]

[UPDATE - Its now 9:35pm. I didnt go out. Im tidying my room. I&apos;ll still go to sleep stoned!]</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music>Ryan Adams - Nuclear</current_music>
<current_mood>determined</current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>6987</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-03 22:50:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-03 14:51:56</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>A sharp new razor
A fresh new cut
A long sleeve tee shirt
And a bandaid for the game

A silent scream
A little tear
A fake smile
And another bad day

The tears wont stop
But the smile is left there
So no one knows
The secret behind my smile

An aching pain
That wont go away
It sits in my heart
It&apos;s there to stay

Seeing the look
Of a disapointed friend
Is the worse feeling ever
But the pain is all thats needed

As selfish as it is
To leave everyone feeling helpless
but everyday and everynight</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>7337</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-05 13:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-05 05:34:17</logtime>
<subject>Harry Potter was really good!</subject>
<event>Yesterday (Friday) I saw the new Harry Potter movie. I wasnt really that excited about it, but my opinion of it certainly changed when I left the cinema. I will say it straight up - that movie was amazing! Nothing like I thought it would be. The effects, the set, the story, the acting and &lt;i&gt;Emma Watson&lt;/i&gt;. WOW she is &lt;B&gt;HOT&lt;/B&gt;
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/movie_posters/Harry_Potter3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Harry Potter&quot;/&gt;

US Premier
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/movie_posters/potter/_40188103_potter_emily220.jpg
&quot; alt=&quot;Emma Watson&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>7599</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-12 14:16:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-15 06:00:35</logtime>
<subject>Buns at Ours</subject>
<event>So, last sunday went really well! I never though our house would be able to fit the whole family. 

A few days later we even got a new dining table and chairs. I think the parents are actually thinking of doing it more often! Fun Fun!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/dining_table.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;New Dining Table&quot; /&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>7908</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-14 16:25:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-15 06:08:16</logtime>
<subject>Its all good!</subject>
<event>Oh God yesterday was fun! I drank lots, talked lots and played football! The latter was definately a &lt;i&gt;bad&lt;/i&gt; idea &apos;cos i &lt;i&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; paid for it this morning! My legs were killing me. I was just feeling really sick when i woke up this morning. Sore head and very sore throat. But it was a damn good day!!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/yay.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;YAY!&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Football_in_the_dark.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Football in the Dark!&quot;/&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/rach_in_tube.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Rachel in a tube, but not underground!&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>7938</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-14 17:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-15 06:47:51</logtime>
<subject>Hay Fever Sucks!</subject>
<event>I have diagnosed myself with having &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.medicinenet.com/script/main/art.asp?articlekey=377&amp;page=1#1whatis&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Hay Fever&lt;/A&gt;. I do seem to have the &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.bbc.co.uk/health/allergy/conditions_hayfever.shtml#symptoms&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;symptoms&lt;/A&gt;:
&lt;UL&gt;
&lt;LI&gt;Runny, sometimes streaming nose. 
&lt;LI&gt;Sneezing. 
&lt;LI&gt;Stuffy, blocked nose. 
&lt;LI&gt;Itching in the throat and nose. 
&lt;LI&gt;Headaches (also known as sinusitis). 
&lt;LI&gt;Watery, itchy, red eyes. 
&lt;LI&gt;Inability to taste or smell food. 
&lt;LI&gt;Disturbed sleep. 
&lt;LI&gt;Itchy ears. 
&lt;/UL&gt;
I&apos;ve had some of these symptoms before, but never as bad as they&apos;ve been recently! Gotta go to Doc and get this sorted.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>8225</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-15 15:42:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-15 07:44:24</logtime>
<subject>The Internet Sucks...</subject>
<event>10:54am - I think it could be time to take a break from the internet. I could put it down to a few reasons for why my life over the last year (or 10 years?) has been on my computer, as well as the fact I have nothing else to do and no where else to go during the week. But now that I am nearly finished school, I will not be spending as much time on the internet at all. I will find another addiction, get another habit. Try watching movies, playing games, pick up the guitar again, may even start reading books! 

What ever it is it will be off the computer. I feel stupid talking to people who don’t use computers/internet as much as I do. Trying to explain to them how good it is is very hard. Explaining how much of a community environment can be found on the internet. Through forums especially, you can talk to hundreds of people and hear what they have to say; sharing opinions, feelings and helping each other. It does feel good talking to a lot of people across the world, finding out that they really aren’t much different from me, that there are people who feel the same as I do. But what I try to remember is that the internet is not real life. 

These are not the people in my life, the people that matter. This is just another way of life, but not the primary one. I sometimes feel that I forget that. Forget how to interact with real people. No ‘LOLs’ and shit like that.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>8567</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-20 18:20:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-20 11:14:31</logtime>
<subject>School&apos;s out for ever!</subject>
<event>FInally, the time has come. I have finished school. 14 years of school over! Only got one more exam to get through on the 29th June, then im done. Hopefully i will get the grades that i need to get onto University. Move away from home and all the shit that i have here, aswell as the good stuff - not very much of that anyway. I just want to be able to start over! I hate it here, hate most aspects of my life. I get hassled when i walk down the fucking street and have little to no friends, i can count in less than one hand the number of real friends...

So anyway... back to now. Im off school! I have many plans for the summer. 
&lt;UL&gt; 
&lt;LI&gt;Sort out my computer and back everything up
&lt;LI&gt;Learn a programming language
&lt;LI&gt;Set up a website
&lt;LI&gt;Read Lots
&lt;LI&gt;Spend lots and lots of time outside 
&lt;LI&gt;Work a lot and get a lot of money
&lt;LI&gt;Get lots of sleep 
&lt;LI&gt;Overall, have a lot of fun!
&lt;/UL&gt; 
So those are the plans, I&apos;ll tell ya if it goes that way in sept/oct.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>8911</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-20 19:41:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-20 12:32:43</logtime>
<subject>So where does that leave me?</subject>
<event>Its sunday, and all the family got together as usual. It wasnt bad. myself, rachel and ronan all just sat and watched tv most of the time, including the sex scenes in &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0115736&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Bound&lt;/A&gt; - such a shit film. Then we watched some of the MTV Move Awards. What pissed me off the most was the fact that when i walked in the first thing ronan said to me was &quot;can i have a cigarette.&quot; I said no, since i didnt have any, and he didnt believe me, then he went really huffy and stormed out. Fuckin waster. Complaining the whole time that he hadnt had a cigarette since last night. Boo Fuckin Hoo. GET A FUCKIN JOB!

Overall i didnt have a bad weekend. On friday i went to ronans house at about 3pm. Played table tennis, bit of basketball, listened to music and watched a bit of tv. Also watched &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0306047/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Scary Movie 3&lt;/A&gt;, which is hilarious.
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/foot_dinosaur.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dont step on it :(&quot;/&gt;

Saturday, was pissy. I got up at about 12. The whole time just waiting until ronan would get up. He got up at 3:30, when we were meant to be meeting Rachel at 4! Then as we were going he decides he doesnt want to go because he has no money, therefore will be bored, wont be able to do anything in town and wont be able to get home. I, for some FUCKED up reason, manage in the end to pursuade him to go. I mean, what the fuck! He really values friendships doesnt he - lazy fucker! He actually would have much rathered stay at home and watch tv - football, big brother etc. I actually wish i had just let him stay at home! 

When we got to town, all he wanted was a smoke. We sat in clements for a while. Then went to a bar for some drinks, where he found some of his friends and stayed talking to them, leaving the two of us on our own, in our &apos;bubble&apos;. Little later we joined em.

So the weekend wasnt that bad overall!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>9014</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-21 15:39:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-21 07:50:35</logtime>
<subject>Longest day of the year...</subject>
<event>Its the 21st June again. The longest day of the year. I was thinking about this over the weekend. Its actually quite depressing really. We all look forward to the summer becuase of the long nights etc. Well if you think about it, it starts getting darker after the 21st June. So technically, tomorrow, and everyday  over the next few months will be darker than the last few days/weeks. I have such a negative view of things dont I. 

Just watched &lt;A HREF=&quot;www.imdb.com/title/tt0169547&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;American Beauty&lt;/A&gt;. What a film. There is such beauty in the world. Among other things it makes me think about the fact that life should be enjoyed for its beauty. Its about enjoying life. Not being stuck in a dead end shit job that you hate all your life. If i dont manage to lead a life in which i am happy, i hope that i am able to turn my life around like Lester did.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>9396</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-21 23:19:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-21 15:22:07</logtime>
<subject>I dont normally do this...</subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://images.quizilla.com/G/ghettokitty/1047299736_entrancing.jpg&quot; border=&quot;0&quot; alt=&quot;entrancing&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;You have an entrancing kiss~ the kind that leaves&lt;br&gt;your partner bedazzled and maybe even feeling&lt;br&gt;he/she is dreaming.  Quite effective; the kiss&lt;br&gt;that never lessens and always blows your&lt;br&gt;partner away like the first time.
&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://quizilla.com/users/ghettokitty/quizzes/What%20kind%20of%20kiss%20are%20you%3F/&quot;&gt; &lt;font size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;What kind of kiss are you?&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;BR&gt; &lt;font size=&quot;-3&quot;&gt;brought to you by &lt;a href=&quot;http://quizilla.com&quot;&gt;Quizilla&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/font&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>9528</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-23 16:57:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-23 09:24:59</logtime>
<subject>Today, I shaved!</subject>
<event>Yea! Look what my mummy bought me! My mummy bought me a razor! 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/philishaverazor.jpg&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>9844</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-24 13:42:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-24 05:50:50</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Personality Test... What have I become?
&lt;P&gt;&lt;table width=&quot;300&quot; cellpadding=&quot;2&quot; cellspacing=&quot;0&quot; border=&quot;0&quot;&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td width=&quot;180&quot;&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Disorder&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td width=&quot;120&quot;&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;b&gt;Rating&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#paranoid&quot;&gt;Paranoid&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#schizoid&quot;&gt;Schizoid&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#schizotypal&quot;&gt;Schizotypal&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#antisocial&quot;&gt;Antisocial&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#000099&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Low&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#borderline&quot;&gt;Borderline&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#990099&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Moderate&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#histrionic&quot;&gt;Histrionic&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#990099&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Moderate&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#narcissistic&quot;&gt;Narcissistic&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#000099&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;Low&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#avoidant&quot;&gt;Avoidant&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#dependent&quot;&gt;Dependent&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/disorder_information2.html#obsessive&quot;&gt;Obsessive-Compulsive&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#cc0033&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;High&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td colspan=&quot;2&quot; align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;&lt;font color=&quot;#000000&quot; face=&quot;arial&quot; size=&quot;-1&quot;&gt;&lt;br&gt;-- &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.4degreez.com/misc/personality_disorder_test.mv&quot;&gt;Personality Disorder Test - Take It!&lt;/a&gt; --&lt;/font&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;br&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>10030</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-24 15:19:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-24 07:37:59</logtime>
<subject>Its really depressing</subject>
<event>I&apos;ve just spent the last hour or so looking through various communities here on LiveJournal and I gotta say I think its really depressing. Yes, I spend a lot of time on my computer, and the internet, but I dont go posting pictures of myself and information about me all over the net for others to read in the hope that I will quite literally be &quot;accepted into their community.&quot; Reading about the information that people post on these things, hoping that they will be &apos;rated highly&apos; or loved by all. And then there are the people who reject others saying stuff like, &quot;no, just no, cos im a bitch and i dont like you,&quot; or &quot;no, your ugly&quot; etc. WHY! 

Why do people look to be accepted by random people half way across the world. These people dont mean shit! Its not these people that matter to you. Will you be happier if these people find you attractive, love your interests and appreciate that you promote their community only so it can go on again in this never ending circle of virtual hatred, bitchiness and love. 

If you want to do it, fine. Just know that these people &lt;i&gt;do&lt;/I&gt; mean shit. They dont know the &lt;I&gt;real&lt;/I&gt; you! Nor do they &lt;I&gt;really&lt;/i&gt; care,</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>10477</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-27 19:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-27 11:08:47</logtime>
<subject>Oh hell... where does we go from here?</subject>
<event>SO everything seems to be getting a bit tiring. I have no money yet again - even though i just got paid on friday. Another month to wait until I get money again. But this time I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; have a lot of money cos i have done a good bit of overtime over the last week and should be doing much more in the weeks to come! 

So this weekend i... worked. When i got home from work yesterday I really felt like doing something, so I went to the cinema to see &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0356150/&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Eurotrip&lt;/A&gt;. I dont really know what to say about this movie. I was really looking forward to it as the trailers looked very very funny, and yes, the film was very very funny... but it certainly wasnt a really amazing film or anything. So i will just say that as a bit of light entertainment, not to be analysed or disected too closely, it was pretty good. 
&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/movie_posters/EuroTrip.jpg&quot;/&gt;

Sunday... work again. Im quite tired at the minute, though i would like to do something other than what i am doing. 

I wanna get high and talk to people...
&lt;p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music>The Chilis!</current_music>
<current_mood>Bored</current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>10574</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-29 15:50:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-29 07:53:35</logtime>
<subject>Oooooh Yeahhh!</subject>
<event>Oh Hell Yeah! Just home from last exam. No More School &lt;B&gt;ever!&lt;/B&gt;

I do feel great!

Now i just gotta concentrate on getting plenty of overtime in work.</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>11002</itemid>
<eventtime>2004-06-30 17:22:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2004-06-30 09:25:04</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;img src=&quot;http://homepage.ntlworld.com/okane000/blog/Eye.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;EYE&quot;/&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
