<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>80772</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-10-06 16:07:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-10-06 15:34:24</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>Hello livejournal, its certainly been a while. 

I must admit though, I havent really missed you... Sorry, but its true. Ive been very busy with proper Blogs and most importantly &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.photoblogs.org&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Photoblogs&lt;/A&gt;. 

Ive been spending every minute of my free time over the last couple of weeks working on the design of &lt;A HREF=&quot;http://www.iced-coffee.com&quot; TARGET=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;my own photoblog&lt;/A&gt; as well as working my way around the vast community of others. 

The internet is such an amazing place. And in many ways it is like a &lt;i&gt;place&lt;/i&gt; as opposed to virtual space of writing and images. Its somewhere so many people go to escape the real world, and find can speak to many people in the real world of their experiences, due to other peoples lack of knowledge of how it all works. 

Its unforuntate really that so many people dont comprehend the extent to which the internet is an amazing place. And for this reason many of my own interests regarding the internet are lost on most people... 

Not fair really.

Anyway - If you check out my site I&apos;ll be very happy :)</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>81122</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-10-10 23:50:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-10-10 22:56:42</logtime>
<subject>update</subject>
<event>Still workin on my website. Truckin along nicely. Last 5 visitors were from Amsterdam, Noord-holland
Stockholm, Singapore, Tampere, Etela-suomen Laani and Tokyo. Nice. 

Also working on normal blog 
&lt;I&gt;A blog or weblog (derived from web + log) is a web-based publication consisting primarily of periodic articles (normally, but not always, in reverse chronological order).&lt;/I&gt;

Everyday making small changes and getting there one step at a time. 

Keeps me sane really. 

In other news. I gotta go to bed cos im working in the morning.</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
