<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>53497</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-01 20:23:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-01 20:29:58</logtime>
<subject>My Name is George W Bush</subject>
<event>Green Day Fucking Rocked!! 

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/Phto0043a.jpg&quot;&gt;
SETLIST
    * &apos;American Idiot&apos;
    * &apos;Jesus Of Suburbia&apos;
    * &apos;Holiday&apos;
    * &apos;Are We The Waiting?&apos;
    * &apos;St Jimmy&apos;
    * &apos;Longview&apos;
    * &apos;Hitchin&apos; A Ride&apos;
    * &apos;Brainstew&apos; / &apos;Jaded&apos;
    * &apos;Knowledge&apos;
    * &apos;Basket Case&apos;
    * &apos;She&apos;
    * &apos;King For A Day&apos;
    * &apos;Wake Me Up When September Ends&apos;
    * &apos;Minority&apos;

    * &apos;Boulevard Of Broken Dreams&apos;
    * &apos;When I Come Around&apos;
    * &apos;We Are The Champions&apos;
    * &apos;Good Riddance (Time Of Your Life)&apos;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/Phto0024.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/Phto0037a.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/Phto0050a.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/PHTO0062.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/Music/greendayticket.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>53717</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-04 23:15:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-04 23:54:13</logtime>
<subject>What a cunt</subject>
<event>It sure isnt nice being blocked and deleted over something very petty, then find out they think I&apos;m really depressing and &quot;he&apos;s the most negative nihilist i&apos;ve ever met.&quot; All I gotta say is - What a cunt!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>53823</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-04 23:55:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-04 23:58:53</logtime>
<subject>Sucks</subject>
<event>My Manager is an Asshole. Such a picky fucking asshole. What a crap 4 hours... 8 hours tomorrow - what fun(!). 

I just dont know what to do. Well I do, mostly. I wanna get back home and outta crappy Derry. Though I like the course Im doing, I guess thats a sacrafice I will have to make. I also really wanna leave now, though my parents feel it could be better for me to stay for the rest of the year, do exams etc and see if it helps me in terms of getting onto other course (at Jordanstown), but i really just wanna leave now. I dont wanna stay in that shit hole on my own - with no internet - anymore!! AHH FUCK!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>54157</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-05 23:35:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-05 23:46:41</logtime>
<subject>Fock!</subject>
<event>Meet the Fockers was funny. Could have been better, but it was still very funnny!!

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/photo_14.jpg&quot;&gt;

&lt;img src=&quot;http://img.photobucket.com/albums/v433/obsoletemind/movies/photo_12.jpg&quot;&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>54403</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-10 15:32:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-10 19:00:08</logtime>
<subject>ScreenSelect</subject>
<event>So a friend told me about Screenselect.co.uk. An online DVD rental site. £9.99 a month, unlimited movies, but only 2 at a time. Free 28-day trial or first 4 free. I signed up on monday. Got my first 2 on Wednesday, watched em and sent em back today. Now I await my next two. I have made a list of the ones I want, so far 114 in list!! 

Its such a great thing. 

Im actually in a rather good mood. Im feeling rather optimistic about the rest of this year... I think I have made my mind up to stay here. I know I&apos;m so fickle, I cant help it. This past week I really havent been bored as much in the same way that I often am. I have watched many dvds, listened to lots of music, watched some crap tv and drank. 

I reserved a place here for next year. I think I can make it work. I will look at the last few months as a learning period, or something like that. I wanna make it work!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>54561</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-16 17:41:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-16 18:09:11</logtime>
<subject>Results...</subject>
<event>I failed. Failed another module. Shit! 

Results out today and ive just checked mine, there was only one I didnt already know, and that makes two I have now failed. One more and im out! I gotta do well this semester - REALLY! 

On a lighter note, I got 60% in test yesterday and i havent been to any of the lectures yet, passed, but still dont know a great deal about it... I gotta do more work on that one. The other two are going ok so far though, but this ones tough. 

Then I got drunk, listened to music, ate chocolate fingers and watched The Breakfast Club on tv at 12:45 and eventually managed to get to sleep at about 5:30. 

Trying to decide whether or not to go out tonight. I think I prob will/should. I mean, I need to be more sociable... that involves going out and spending a little money. Its the only way...</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>54803</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-18 23:04:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-18 23:08:59</logtime>
<subject>&quot;Alright, whats the craic?&quot;</subject>
<event>Someone please tell me what the fuck that means!! You know when someone walks down the road and says that to you, but they still walk on. Am I supposed to answer? Or should I just answer with, &quot;Alright, hows it goin?&quot; or &quot;hows the craic?&quot; I just dont know. It happens [almost] every day and i dont know what to say... If anyone has any suggestions as to how to answer the ignorant assholes in the world when they say this please tell me!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>55112</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-20 14:37:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-20 15:23:39</logtime>
<subject>Golden</subject>
<event>Yesterday was my grandparents 50TH ANNIVERSARY! Thats a hell of a long time. 

Party was last night. Much drinking and talking to old people was done by me. Didnt get too drunk though, cos i had to get up at 9am this morning. And I did, and i was a little tired, though wasnt too tired throughout work. 

Off to watch the Snooker final. Later</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>55485</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-22 01:00:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-23 15:01:51</logtime>
<subject>Drunk...</subject>
<event>Its exactly 1am on Tuesday 22nd February. 

I am at my happiest when ive drunk a 1/2 bottle of vodka and coke and I listen to music!! 

The Red Hot Chili Peppers 
Bush 
Matchbox 20
Placebo
Our Lady Peace
Muse 
Etc...

Its allll good!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>55598</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-23 15:02:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-23 15:05:42</logtime>
<subject>Backdated</subject>
<event>22:37 - Tuesday

I guess you could certainly call that snow! yup, its snowin&apos; outside! I hope it lies - cos i have no class tomorrow! But knowing this crappy place and its crappy weather it probably wont... 

Im listening to &apos;Marilyn Manson - Sweet Dreams.&apos; Ive been listening to/watching Mansons music videos for over an hour now - I fuckin love that guy! I wanna be as cool as HIM!! 

Ive also been drinking too. I amm the makings of an alcoholic. Ive almost finished a 1/2 bottle in 1 1/2 hours. I dont even feel as drunk as i want to be. Enough to decide to write this shit down, but raaaaaaghhhh, not enough....... 

That snow&apos;s fairly think, but theres too much damn rain/wetness on the ground for it to lie. 

I want some fucking drugs. Dope and pills. I really do. Bein here in my room all the time i just drink cos i need something. If anyone out there can get me anything please tell me. 

Time for a cigarettte!

Like the Channel 4 ad i just watched: my life motto: &quot;TO BE HAPPY!!&quot;

Yup just spent the last few mins txting people..... sad maybe... do I give a fuck, apparently not. My virtual friends rock!! 

Every time I look at my black nails i smile......

HAHAHAHA &apos;Spotlight on BBC1 is &quot;Spotlighting&quot; Gay Priests! HA

FUUUUUUUUUUUUCKK!!!!!! 
i JUST SPILT MY LAST GLASSS OF VODKA AND COKE...... FUCK!!!!!!!

i MEAN, WHY THE FUCK CANT I GET ALCOHOL WHENEVER THE FUCK I WANT! fUCKIN&apos; OFFLICENSE CLOSES AT 9:30 - HOW FUCKING GAY IS THAT!!!!!! AAAGHHHHHHHHHHH!!!!!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>55956</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-25 14:33:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-25 14:36:26</logtime>
<subject>Thursday</subject>
<event>What a night. Im not long up - and not in my own house either. 

I was completely pissed. I had a great night... just wish birthday girl had as much fun as I did. Hope things work out Christine!</event>
<security>usemask</security>
<allowmask>1</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>56167</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-02-26 23:34:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-02-26 23:35:34</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>If i ask nicely will you comment on my entries?</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
