<?xml version="1.0" encoding='utf-8'?>
<livejournal>
<entry>
<itemid>71814</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-18 14:56:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-18 19:07:58</logtime>
<subject>Last Night</subject>
<event>Only one more night in america. Im very very sad. Been depressed about it a couple of days ago, but now i just cant wait to go out and get drunk tonight. 

Well i havent updated in quite a while. 

It was my birthday on Friday. We went to NYC on friday, which was so much fun. Train into Grand Central, walk  to Time Square, then took a romantic horse and carriage ride through Central Park. That night we went to one of the greatest bars ever at the bottom of Manhatten with an amazing view of the George Washington Bridge. I got so wasted and puked and slept on the subway! Thats an achievment!!

As for the rest of the time - Its just been great! Great friends! Good-times! I dont want to leave!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>71966</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-22 08:30:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-22 08:15:23</logtime>
<subject>Now what?</subject>
<event>So Ive been home for two days now and i really dont want to be here. 

It was definately the greatest time of my life. I made great friends and learnt a lot. Now i want to change a lot about myself and my lifestyle. Most importantly I wanna save to go back! 

But until then i am trying to think of how i can achieve the changes i want to make. Its a nice thought... but until i actually get some money i cant really do anything. Though the first thing i am doing is looking for another job. I also wanna spend less time online... easier said than done. Gonna try my hand at reading. I hear its fun. 

Until then Im at quite a loss. Maybe it was just so good &apos;cos I was on vacation, but i am sure that im able to see past that and it could be much better than this shit-hole. The point is; i wont be here all my life.

This is my life and theres only me. The only person i gotta please is myself. Im not happy and im going to do something about it!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>72209</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-24 14:37:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-24 14:06:19</logtime>
<subject>No more drink</subject>
<event>Im not gonna have more than 3 drinks for at least 2 months when I go out!
Well infact im not going to go out for at least 3 weeks! I cant afford it! 

Massive withdrawals setting in. I wanna go back! 

I have decided im going to take driving lessons. I &lt;i&gt;will&lt;/i&gt; be able to drive by june!   


&lt;CENTER&gt;&lt;i&gt;&quot;Just trollin&apos; around the dance floor
Puts a big smile on my face
It ain&apos;t too far, come as you are

An old jukebox and a real bad band
We got waitresses and we got barflies
A dumb-ass and a wise-guy
If you get too drunk just sleep out in your car

&quot;I just love it&quot;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/CENTER&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>72477</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-25 12:24:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-25 11:28:18</logtime>
<subject></subject>
<event>&lt;font size=&quot;5&quot;&gt;Damn iPod - why wont you work!! RARRRGH!!&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/font&gt;</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>72942</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-26 16:31:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-26 15:36:38</logtime>
<subject>Bad iPod, Bad!</subject>
<event>I got my packaging to send my iPod back to Apple for a replacement. 

Right now im Restoring it to factoring settings (wiping it). It better not take long! And the replacement better work!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
<entry>
<itemid>72971</itemid>
<eventtime>2005-07-29 22:05:00</eventtime>
<logtime>2005-07-29 21:11:14</logtime>
<subject>I hate smoking!</subject>
<event>Why is it that every time ive had a cigarette when ive been drinking in the last couple of weeks ive almost gagged - like, really almost been sick! I dont like it. Damn I fuckin hate smoking!!</event>
<security>public</security>
<allowmask>0</allowmask>
<current_music></current_music>
<current_mood></current_mood>
</entry>
</livejournal>
